[{"key": 1, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "2 February 2022", "question": "Related to technology which I have worked", "answer": []}, {"key": 2, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Bonusly", "date": "2 February 2022", "question": "Describe a situation where you made a mistake.  How did you handle it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 3, "position": "Azure Security Engineer", "company": "Mindtree", "date": "31 January 2022", "question": "When to connect two VM's if we have to enter the routing table?\r\nOn asking I am sorry can you please repeat the question again his reply was ok let's move to next:\r\nWhat is the use of Key Bolt?\r\nThird what scripting do you use in the routing table?", "answer": []}, {"key": 4, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sitel Group", "date": "30 January 2022", "question": "What are the three pillars of information security ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 5, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Radiometer", "date": "29 January 2022", "question": "Product security lifecycle, everything around. How will you work around with the security phase?", "answer": []}, {"key": 6, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "28 January 2022", "question": "Most questions were talking about challenges/problems solved at previous jobs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 7, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "TikTok", "date": "28 January 2022", "question": "Coding interview: To write a program to determine highest profitable stock.", "answer": []}, {"key": 8, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Optimizely", "date": "27 January 2022", "question": "Can you tell me about project X on your resume?", "answer": []}, {"key": 9, "position": "Security Pre-sales Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "26 January 2022", "question": "Where would you look if you're looking for passwords on a Linux system?", "answer": []}, {"key": 10, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "HashiCorp", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "\u201cWhat is your biggest Weakness?\u201d\r\n\u201cWhy Hashicorp?\u201d", "answer": []}, {"key": 11, "position": "Cyber Security Risk Engineer", "company": "S&P Global", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "I was asked about my overall work  experience along with technical and scenario-based questions related to my role", "answer": []}, {"key": 12, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Equifax", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about your experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 13, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "DBS Bank", "date": "24 January 2022", "question": "What is the most challenging task you faced", "answer": []}, {"key": 14, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "24 January 2022", "question": "Basics of information security and nothing to worry about.", "answer": []}, {"key": 15, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Boeing", "date": "23 January 2022", "question": "how to work in team\r\none technical question", "answer": []}, {"key": 16, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "23 January 2022", "question": "Are you willing to relocate?", "answer": []}, {"key": 17, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Komodo Health", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "In the coding interview we covered getting information for AWS logs/data in two exercises", "answer": []}, {"key": 18, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "Questions about OWASP Top-10 . . .", "answer": []}, {"key": 19, "position": "Senior Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "Coinbase", "date": "19 January 2022", "question": "What happens when you go to Google and type in a search?\r\n\r\nWhat would you recommend for a simple web app for session management, and right now all it can do is login with a username and password?\r\n\r\nWhat are two ways your Coinbase Wallet could be vulnerable?", "answer": []}, {"key": 20, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "18 January 2022", "question": "Networking, SDLC, Kubernetes, security fundamentals and aws cloud environment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 21, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "DOCK", "date": "18 January 2022", "question": "Quem \u00e9 voc\u00ea? \r\nO que voc\u00ea faz ?", "answer": ["Sou um estudante dedicado que aprende muito r\u00e1pido e procuro fazer tudo com muito esfor\u00e7o e dedica\u00e7\u00e3o Less"]}, {"key": 22, "position": "Security Tier II Systems Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "17 January 2022", "question": "In a high level details about devices functionality and path  packet flow regarding VPN and Firepower were asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 23, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "17 January 2022", "question": "1. Searching and sorting algorithms\n2. Database concepts\n3. Java OOPs concepts\n4. Security related questions\n5. Projects\n6.Internship questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 24, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 January 2022", "question": "What's is the difference between synchronous encryption and asynchronous encryption? \r\n\r\nWhat steps do you take during an incident?", "answer": []}, {"key": 25, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Orlando Health", "date": "14 January 2022", "question": "Why is powershell better than the command line?", "answer": []}, {"key": 26, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "13 January 2022", "question": "There was one small application, and task was to do code review.", "answer": []}, {"key": 27, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Shutterfly", "date": "12 January 2022", "question": "related to my previous work and technical  questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 28, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "10 January 2022", "question": "How many years of experience?", "answer": ["2"]}, {"key": 29, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ASAPP", "date": "8 January 2022", "question": "programar una lambda en aws usando servicios como sqs, borrar security groups no utlizados", "answer": []}, {"key": 30, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "8 January 2022", "question": "Questions about SQL Injection asked to write a script to count lines of code and a customer service-oriented question.", "answer": []}, {"key": 31, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "7 January 2022", "question": "what do you know about twilio?", "answer": []}, {"key": 32, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "7 January 2022", "question": "Apart from the technical questions, one that let me thinking is \"what would you do in this pandemic times where everyone is working remotely, so they could getting to know who you are or what you do\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 33, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "OpenTable", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Salary expectations\r\nExperience \r\nPast projects", "answer": []}, {"key": 34, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Miro", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Use your time to understand responsibilities and expectations from your role, the team is open to give clear answers. And of course, have a flashback of significant moments of your past job experiences before the interviews.", "answer": []}, {"key": 35, "position": "Android Security Engineer", "company": "Robinhood", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Does not apply to the situation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 36, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Describe what this code is doing/ what is the attacker trying to do to obfuscate this malware", "answer": []}, {"key": 37, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Describe what this code is doing/ what is the attacker trying to do to obfuscate this malware", "answer": []}, {"key": 38, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Outschool", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "What are the differences between SSL and TLS?", "answer": ["SSL 3.0 and TLS 1.0 are nearly identical. Otherwise, TLS is the newer standard and the one that should be followed. Less"]}, {"key": 39, "position": "IT Operations and Security Engineer", "company": "Arabesque ", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Why did you apply? What are you looking for in the role? etc; etc;", "answer": []}, {"key": 40, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Caterpillar", "date": "5 January 2022", "question": "How is Serena Williams doing right now ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 41, "position": "Senior Security Systems Engineer", "company": "Blackboard", "date": "4 January 2022", "question": "how to secure cloud infraestucture?", "answer": []}, {"key": 42, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Edward Jones", "date": "3 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about a time you had to reach out to team members for assistance with a problem, and what you did with the help they provided.", "answer": []}, {"key": 43, "position": "Graduate Engineer Security Cyber Defense", "company": "ANZ Bank", "date": "3 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about the projects you did.\nYour Hobbies\nWhy do u want to join ANZ.\nWhat field u r interested in", "answer": []}, {"key": 44, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HubSpot", "date": "2 January 2022", "question": "A lot of \"tell me about a time when...\" questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 45, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "CertiK", "date": "1 January 2022", "question": "Past experience, Have any questions for the interviewer", "answer": []}, {"key": 46, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Spiff", "date": "30 December 2021", "question": "Q: Tell me about yourself\nQ: Where do you see yourself in 1, 3, 5 years?\nQ: What specifically have you contributed to benefit your team/organization", "answer": []}, {"key": 47, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "29 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are main components of \"secure\" in SSDLC, what 3 top things in terms of processes, controls or whatever would you recommend to start securing existing SDLC?", "answer": []}, {"key": 48, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "JupiterOne", "date": "28 December 2021", "question": "Have you worked with any data streaming tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 49, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "JupiterOne", "date": "28 December 2021", "question": "Have you used any IaC tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 50, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Comcast", "date": "27 December 2021", "question": "All about Endpoint Security and security technologies", "answer": []}, {"key": 51, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "23 December 2021", "question": "Tell me how a server connects to another server", "answer": []}, {"key": 52, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dave", "date": "23 December 2021", "question": "Q: How to integrate local domain and cloud provider credentials", "answer": []}, {"key": 53, "position": "Network Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Rakuten", "date": "22 December 2021", "question": "Asa packet flow and networking security concepts", "answer": []}, {"key": 54, "position": "Security Signature Engineer", "company": "Qualys", "date": "21 December 2021", "question": "Basically related to OWASP Top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 55, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Wildlife Studios", "date": "21 December 2021", "question": "How asymmetric encryption works?\nDescribe in details an SQL injections\nChoose any vulnerability you want  and fully describe it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 56, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Partners Group", "date": "17 December 2021", "question": "Some basics questions about IT security, DevOps with a case study about AWS + IT Security incident handling", "answer": []}, {"key": 57, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "17 December 2021", "question": "I will respect the NDA.\nQuestions are just as you would imagine as a security engineer. Don't hesitate to ask your recruiter for basic guidance on how to best prepare.", "answer": []}, {"key": 58, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "Asked to hack into a fake website.", "answer": []}, {"key": 59, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Vonage", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "General questions related to security, cloud, Linux", "answer": []}, {"key": 60, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "Leetcode type Coding  challenge of medium - hard difficulty.", "answer": []}, {"key": 61, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "12 December 2021", "question": "Top 10 OWASP list and their description", "answer": []}, {"key": 62, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Web3 Foundation", "date": "12 December 2021", "question": "how would you start investigating a spoofed email (that seemed to come from the company's domain)?\r\nhow to perform transaction signing on a k8s cluster\r\nhow polkadot works and difference with bitcoin and ethereum", "answer": []}, {"key": 63, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Yell", "date": "11 December 2021", "question": "what are the stages you would go through when responding to a security incident", "answer": []}, {"key": 64, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 December 2021", "question": "Generic security engineering questions. No need to dig into the details", "answer": []}, {"key": 65, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "What is method overloading?\nWhat is method overriding?\nDifference between c and c++", "answer": []}, {"key": 66, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "Leetcode medium array related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 67, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Loginsoft", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "All technical and practical questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 68, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 December 2021", "question": "Q: What do you want to do for the next few years in your career?\nQ: What's the most interesting security issue you found?", "answer": []}, {"key": 69, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "Nokia", "date": "8 December 2021", "question": "Focus was on my experience so far and what technologies I used before", "answer": []}, {"key": 70, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "7 December 2021", "question": "\"Say something about yourself......\" was the first question,\ngetting an overview of my resume, further questions were asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 71, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "3 December 2021", "question": "Basic networking knowledge, port numbers, appliance topology, and more.", "answer": []}, {"key": 72, "position": "Devops Security Engineer", "company": "HubSpot", "date": "2 December 2021", "question": "They asked me to solve a specific question.", "answer": []}, {"key": 73, "position": "Security Response Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "2 December 2021", "question": "Web application vulnerabilities and common attacks", "answer": ["Easy"]}, {"key": 74, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Ebryx", "date": "1 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are the different network layer attacks I know of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 75, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Ebryx", "date": "1 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are the different network layer attacks I know of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 76, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MassMutual", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 77, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MassMutual", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 78, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "BitGo", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "The questions I wasn\u2019t able to answer clearly involved supply-chain attacks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 79, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "they ask whether I know anything about Huawei cloud", "answer": []}, {"key": 80, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "they ask whether I know anything about Huawei cloud", "answer": []}, {"key": 81, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Cerebral (CA)", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "The interview did not actually happen", "answer": []}, {"key": 82, "position": "Senior Analyst Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "I was asked questions about real world implementation of Fourier series, a few things about computer network.", "answer": []}, {"key": 83, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "6sense", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "I had total 10 rounds of interview, each round was based on the last round, interview had both theoretical as well as practical rounds. For security you have to be well versed in end to end security, including:\n1. DevOps security\n2. Application Security\n3. Infrastructure security\n4. Shell scripting.\n5. Penetration testing.\n6. AWS modules and security as a code.\n7. Policies and preventions.\n8. Coding - python, ansible, yara rules", "answer": ["Explain about each of these process as they ask about and I did well in them."]}, {"key": 84, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "28 November 2021", "question": "Code review, general security questions, AWS/cloud security, SSRF, secure design/threat modeling questions, behavior questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 85, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Conductor", "date": "26 November 2021", "question": "How would you act in case of incident?", "answer": []}, {"key": 86, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 November 2021", "question": "OWASP 10 (xss, csrf)\ncryptography(explain PKI, diffie hellman)\nlots of behavioral questions for more than 50% of the time.\nCoding round was pretty simple, asked for a simple loop, no harder than leetcode easy", "answer": []}, {"key": 87, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Hexaware Technologies", "date": "25 November 2021", "question": "Azure  Cloud Security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 88, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ID.me", "date": "24 November 2021", "question": "Describe a situation where you failed and what did you do to handle it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 89, "position": "Software Engineer (Security Platform)", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "24 November 2021", "question": "No real questions, simply saying i dont meet the criteria of hiring and thats about it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 90, "position": "Cloud Security Operations Engineer", "company": "2nd Watch", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Pen testing phases/stages \nExplain ARP poisoning\nBasic security questions (CIA, hashing,etc)", "answer": []}, {"key": 91, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Kajabi", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Application Security Engineer questions, web app vulnerability management, code review, security's role in SDLC.", "answer": []}, {"key": 92, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Bridgewater Associates", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "They asked questions that were on point with the job description, there were no \"gotcha\" type questions. The recruiter was very clear as to what to expect when speaking with other team members.", "answer": []}, {"key": 93, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Reddit", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Nothing to do with cloud/security engineering at all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 94, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "CyberCoders", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Recruiter asked about experience in each of the job requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 95, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Describe why you think diversity is important.", "answer": ["I virtue-signaled with my typical answer that let them know I really do consider harmonious diversity a strength.  (And I do.) Less"]}, {"key": 96, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Describe why you think diversity is important.", "answer": ["I virtue-signaled with my typical answer that let them know I really do consider harmonious diversity a strength.  (And I do.) Less"]}, {"key": 97, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "Question about a project from your resume and then build upon the technical aspects of it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 98, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "Question about a project from your resume and then build upon the technical aspects of it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 99, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Amadeus", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "How does Diffie Hellman work?\nIP subnetting\nChange management process and incident recovery experience\nFirewall and proxy experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 100, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "Talk about your experience with McAfee products.", "answer": []}, {"key": 101, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "Have you ever work with requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 102, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "What is your knowledge on agile projects?", "answer": []}, {"key": 103, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "14 November 2021", "question": "Deep understanding of common classes of product security vulnerabilities and attack/ defence methodologies.\nknowledge of the security development lifecycle and threat modelling process", "answer": []}, {"key": 104, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "BigID", "date": "12 November 2021", "question": "The BigID interview process did have some technical aspects for the role in question, but it was mostly about getting a feel for the culture, and whether or not I would be a good fit for them, and vice versa.", "answer": []}, {"key": 105, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Unified Healthcare Group", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Talk about the Owasp top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 106, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hotstar", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Most of questions were scenario-based and not routine questions about attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 107, "position": "Security Software Developer", "company": "SafeBreach", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Home excersize is a good representation for the job requirements and entailed implementing a small PoC of an attack on an existing windows system mechanism.\nInterview contained several questions around networking and protocols.", "answer": []}, {"key": 108, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Redox, Inc.", "date": "10 November 2021", "question": "1. What are your personal principles and strategies to reduce vulnerabilities introduced into production?\n2. How do you stay up to date with new/emerging technology?\n\nOther than that, it was fairly straightforward.  No coding, all situational (Describe a time where...).  Be ready for an ongoing conversation, and diving deeper into each of your answers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 109, "position": "Product Security Software Engineer", "company": "Varian Medical Systems", "date": "10 November 2021", "question": "How do you tell if a vulnerability has high impact?", "answer": []}, {"key": 110, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "In my opinion expected salary doesn't fit their requirement", "answer": ["The main problem is that, nobody didn't gave me except reason why I didn't selected Less"]}, {"key": 111, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AGIO", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "Questions about SIEM, XDR, incident response", "answer": []}, {"key": 112, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NIKE", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "Qualities of a good manager", "answer": []}, {"key": 113, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "1Password", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Explain Encryption, Hashing, and encoding.", "answer": ["Know what they are and what they are used for protect."]}, {"key": 114, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "How would you protect a house from outsiders?", "answer": ["Go through this systematically and logically"]}, {"key": 115, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Paran\u00e1 Banco", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Cite algum desafio.", "answer": []}, {"key": 116, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cognite", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Risk assessment process and life cy", "answer": []}, {"key": 117, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cognite", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Risk assessment process and life cy", "answer": []}, {"key": 118, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HCL Technologies", "date": "6 November 2021", "question": "tools you have worked on mostly on ATP. and how to whitelist and all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 119, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "6 November 2021", "question": "Implement a linked list and then implement an algorithm that says if theres a loop.\nThere was another one but I forgot.", "answer": []}, {"key": 120, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Trulioo", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "1. One of encryption method algorithm\r\n2. Hashing method\r\n3. Live coding challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 121, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "There were code reviews and questions about how to design secure environments", "answer": []}, {"key": 122, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "FloQast", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "What is a CSRF attack?", "answer": ["Wasn\u2019t asked about how to prevent it."]}, {"key": 123, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Beyond Identity", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "Web security, DEP, ASLR, SAML, OIDC, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 124, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dell Technologies", "date": "3 November 2021", "question": "Very basic cybersecurity questions, networking, etc...", "answer": []}, {"key": 125, "position": "Staff Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Very Good Security", "date": "3 November 2021", "question": "You receive a security alert for activity on a system, how do you go about triaging, investigating, and then responding to the incident. \r\n\r\nBasically asked to detail different aspects of the IR lifecycle.", "answer": []}, {"key": 126, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What is perfect forward secrecy in the TLS protocol?", "answer": []}, {"key": 127, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What is the difference between strongly-typed and weakly-typed programming languages and can you give an example?", "answer": []}, {"key": 128, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What kind of cryptography TLS protocol uses (asymmetric-key, symmetric-key, both)?", "answer": []}, {"key": 129, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ByteDance", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Gave a sample post request and ask to explain on the possible exploitation", "answer": []}, {"key": 130, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Clark (Germany)", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "Introduce yourself.\nPast Experience. \nTechnologies I have worked on.", "answer": []}, {"key": 131, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Kiratech", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "Chi \u00e8 per te il DevOps", "answer": []}, {"key": 132, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "What is somsth you have learned recently and how did you apply it to the workplace.", "answer": []}, {"key": 133, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Nuna", "date": "30 October 2021", "question": "The interviews were nicely divided and not repetetive. They tried to know me not only technically but also had beavioral questions.\r\n\r\nInitial interviews were about my experience, my current role, what are my interests, why am I looking for a change, etc.\r\n\r\nSome of the technological questions were on topics such as:\r\nOIDC, SAML, SSO, AWS, S3, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 134, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "27 October 2021", "question": "as usual first will be 2 technical rounds and after that HR round", "answer": []}, {"key": 135, "position": "Security Operations Engineer - SOE", "company": "Blend", "date": "26 October 2021", "question": "How do you match Blends culture?", "answer": []}, {"key": 136, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "25 October 2021", "question": "Know and understand the company's values and how it applies to you.", "answer": []}, {"key": 137, "position": "Cloud Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Teradata", "date": "22 October 2021", "question": "Can you tell me of a project that you recently worked on that you are proud of?", "answer": ["I described one of the projects that I had recently worked on."]}, {"key": 138, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "20 October 2021", "question": "Terraform policies for collaboration\nAnsible roles \nScript challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 139, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Honeywell", "date": "20 October 2021", "question": "Tell us why you would like to work for Honeywell and why you are interested in this role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 140, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Unqork", "date": "19 October 2021", "question": "Tell me about how you would approach a web app for testing.", "answer": []}, {"key": 141, "position": "Security Compliance Engineer", "company": "Typeform", "date": "19 October 2021", "question": "Why I was in the hiring process (context: I had joined the previous company just 4,5 months before).", "answer": ["I did a research about Typeform's history, services, values, philosophy, etc., and not just the position, but the company itself motivated me to try to join Typeform. Less"]}, {"key": 142, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CENSUS", "date": "17 October 2021", "question": "Technical challenge in C, memory allocation questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 143, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "ExamWorks", "date": "16 October 2021", "question": "What are your salary expectations?", "answer": []}, {"key": 144, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "15 October 2021", "question": "What is your cyber security related experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 145, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Figma", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "Coding Challenge to be completed in less than 2 hours requiring research and mathematical algorithms.", "answer": []}, {"key": 146, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "What are the  different types of encryption.", "answer": []}, {"key": 147, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "The second round just go through a simple code interview (sorting) and cyber security-related questions (identify CVE etc).", "answer": []}, {"key": 148, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "Fully Technical Security related question", "answer": []}, {"key": 149, "position": "Sales Engineer ( Trust and Security)", "company": "Bugcrowd", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "your role in sales cycle", "answer": ["answer thru experience"]}, {"key": 150, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Coinbase", "date": "12 October 2021", "question": "Describe what happens when I type 'google.com' into a web browser.", "answer": []}, {"key": 151, "position": "Fire and Security Service Engineer", "company": "Reflexis Systems", "date": "11 October 2021", "question": "What size of systems have you worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 152, "position": "Senior IT Security Engineer", "company": "GEODIS", "date": "7 October 2021", "question": "What is your salary expectation for this position based on your experience?", "answer": ["I didn't provide a hard number, because I don't have all the information available to accurately assess the value of a compensation package. Less"]}, {"key": 153, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "7 October 2021", "question": "General security questions, environments and technologies I worked with.", "answer": []}, {"key": 154, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Was asked to indentify real-word vulnerabilities in prints of source code.", "answer": []}, {"key": 155, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Tell me About yourself\nWhere do you see yourself in 5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 156, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Deep technical questions on offensive security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 157, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Deep technical questions on offensive security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 158, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Providence Health Care", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Authentication resumed based questions regarding my skills", "answer": []}, {"key": 159, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "Herjavec Group", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Work experience with practical application?", "answer": []}, {"key": 160, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Saint-Gobain", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Working of the firewalls and proxies", "answer": []}, {"key": 161, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "Amazon", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "LP, Threat Modeling, Pen testing scenario, code review, PKI", "answer": ["what's LP?"]}, {"key": 162, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "Specific questions about the OSI Model and how to analyze security logs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 163, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sourcegraph", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "Describe a situation in which conflict occurred and how you addressed it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 164, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "4 October 2021", "question": "What was a time you dealt with a stressful situation? How did you overcome this?", "answer": ["Discussed a specific customer support engagement that was severely escalated. Addressed the issue with clear communication and expectations until resolution. Less"]}, {"key": 165, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "4 October 2021", "question": "Basic security questions, like TCP handshakes, how does ssh work, what tools used !!\n\nHave you done threat model and code review etc. \n\n80% of the interview was businessy questions such as: \"tell me about a time you took a risk at work\" etc.\n\n(I am not sure why a technical position didn't have more technical questions and less leadership questions )", "answer": []}, {"key": 166, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "1 October 2021", "question": "The interview questions were mostly open-ended, which gives candidates a chance to show their strengths.", "answer": []}, {"key": 167, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "1 October 2021", "question": "The interview questions were mostly open-ended, which gives candidates a chance to show their strengths.", "answer": []}, {"key": 168, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Frame.io", "date": "30 September 2021", "question": "1- Describe the most innovative project I lead \n2- How would my team members describe me \n3- AWS Cloud Security questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 169, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "30 September 2021", "question": "What would you recommend to mitigate risk of MITM attack on a web application?", "answer": []}, {"key": 170, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "cannot discuss due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 171, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "The technical questions included designing some real life feature from a security perspective.", "answer": []}, {"key": 172, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Klarna", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "general security questions about DDoS, cryptography", "answer": []}, {"key": 173, "position": "Software Engineer - Security", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "A junior engineer asked me a few cultural fit questions and then dived into system design for 40 min. He asked me to design Doordash. + Uber backend, \r\n\r\nHad a good conversation. But i felt the interviewer did not have much experience. He knew the basic stuff of NoSQL vs RDS, Caching, LB etc.\r\n\r\nOverall the tech screen was good.", "answer": []}, {"key": 174, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Communications", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Technicals fundamental questions were asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 175, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Communications", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Senario based questions were asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 176, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Basics of networking, cybersecurity, and questions based on the CV.", "answer": []}, {"key": 177, "position": "Security Research Engineer", "company": "Lojas Riachuelo", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Related to security question it was", "answer": ["Uses of stack"]}, {"key": 178, "position": "Software Developer - Security Team", "company": "Grab", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Online Test:\r\nIt comprised of 3 problem solving coding questions, testing knowledge of typical DS/Algos. Time allotted for the test is sufficient.\r\nCoding: Standard DS/Algos are sufficient to come up with the sol.", "answer": []}, {"key": 179, "position": "Network Security/SASE Engineer", "company": "Aruba Networks", "date": "27 September 2021", "question": "C programming (Traverse a Binary Search Tree, Insertion in Binary Tree, Best day to buy and Sell stock in Linear Time), System Design: File hosting for 100-500 people", "answer": []}, {"key": 180, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Ocado Group", "date": "27 September 2021", "question": "Technical questions about encryption and data protection", "answer": []}, {"key": 181, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "26 September 2021", "question": "Cloudflare magic transit and how it works", "answer": []}, {"key": 182, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Microland", "date": "25 September 2021", "question": "What is the ospf cost", "answer": ["It's 110"]}, {"key": 183, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "24 September 2021", "question": "The questions were related to dev ops and programming.", "answer": []}, {"key": 184, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "24 September 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 185, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Eyeo", "date": "23 September 2021", "question": "Do you think a 2FA implementation is a perfect/unbreakable solution for all the problems considering authentication? Could there be issues regarding 2FAs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 186, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CSG", "date": "23 September 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself and about your work experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 187, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "CSS Corporation", "date": "22 September 2021", "question": "Ccna, tcp ip, routing switching", "answer": []}, {"key": 188, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GlaxoSmithKline", "date": "20 September 2021", "question": "Technical question related to understanding of cybersecurity, networking & firewall.", "answer": []}, {"key": 189, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "20 September 2021", "question": "How would I empty an airplane filled with jelly beans.", "answer": []}, {"key": 190, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "18 September 2021", "question": "Comment vous voyez vous dans 5 ans chez EY?", "answer": []}, {"key": 191, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cognizant Technology Solutions", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "Introduce about yourself, about the projects done in college.", "answer": []}, {"key": 192, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BayCare Health System", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 193, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Navi Technologies", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "How to secure communication between AWS and GCP", "answer": []}, {"key": 194, "position": "Engineer II - Security", "company": "Verizon", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "What is Second Order SQLi?", "answer": []}, {"key": 195, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sdgc", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "what is OWASP TOP 10 ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 196, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Banyan Data Services", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "what is called as web application ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 197, "position": "Summer: Software, Platform Or Security Engineer", "company": "BP", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "What interests you in working in software development?", "answer": ["I got into coding during the summer of 2020 when my internship had been cancelled, and I started to love working on my own mini projects while learning how to code at the same time. I like the work flow of designing, drafting, troubleshooting and then iterating on your work to add features and make it more efficient. Each design challenge is like a puzzle that I get great enjoyment from solving. Working on bigger, more collaborative projects would be beneficial to me as I could improve my understanding of best principles for designing the architecture of a software. Less"]}, {"key": 198, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Esper", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "1. Gave two coding questions and asked for code optimization\n2. Have you worked on firewall", "answer": []}, {"key": 199, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "Tell me about your experience and background", "answer": []}, {"key": 200, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "What do you like to do outside of security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 201, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "What's one of your greatest challenges.", "answer": []}, {"key": 202, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "what is scalability in cloud?", "answer": ["scalability is one of the main moto of cloud providers. we can easily scale in or scale out our resources based on our own requirements. Less"]}, {"key": 203, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Blu", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "Me fale um pouco sobre suas experi\u00eancias?\nConte o que voc\u00ea espera para essa vaga?\nQuais s\u00e3o suas motiva\u00e7\u00f5es?", "answer": []}, {"key": 204, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Reddit", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "There were no technical questions, just \"why do you want to work at Reddit\", or \"how would you explain XYZ to someone\". Questions similar to that.", "answer": []}, {"key": 205, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ActioNet", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "CISSP Credentials are required for this role, where are you in your CPE cycle?", "answer": []}, {"key": 206, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Locuz Enterprise Solutions", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "Please go through the fundamental concepts of Network and Network Security domain.", "answer": []}, {"key": 207, "position": "\u200bSecurity Research Software Developer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "Basic OOP questions in python.", "answer": []}, {"key": 208, "position": "Security Engineer - Red Team", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 September 2021", "question": "Asked trivia questions like \u201cwhat is the underlying file type of office macros\u201d and \u201cwhat is the file type extension of modern office files\u201d", "answer": ["Many similar trivia questions were asked"]}, {"key": 209, "position": "Security Engineer - Red Team", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 September 2021", "question": "Asked detailed questions about windows API and exploit development. Must know exact function names off the top of your head", "answer": ["Seemed like they were looking for hobbyist malware developers and 0day hunters"]}, {"key": 210, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Marqeta", "date": "10 September 2021", "question": "any failed projects that worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 211, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "10 September 2021", "question": "Knowledge on ISO 27001 standard and specifications", "answer": []}, {"key": 212, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Westcon-Comstor", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "What are your interests in security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 213, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Different kinds of XSS and how to fix them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 214, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Philip Morris International", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Difference between SAST and DAST from vulnerability identification perspective? Limitations in both approaches.", "answer": []}, {"key": 215, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "GeniusRx", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "The 2 ladies in HR kept talking about the company history and \"personalities\" but had no questions.  The only question was \"do you have any question for me\" to which  I asked a couple of questions and both ladies were completely clueless.", "answer": []}, {"key": 216, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "MyFitnessPal", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Describe a time when a project had a major hurdle and how did you overcome that hurdle.", "answer": ["I gave an honest answer about a problem with interdepartmental relationships"]}, {"key": 217, "position": "Lead Security Engineer, Cyber CloudOps", "company": "Circle Internet Financial", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "Do you know how to write in golang?", "answer": ["No.. why would I."]}, {"key": 218, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Safelite AutoGlass", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "Mostly typical interview question for a position like this.", "answer": ["I thin I answered them well."]}, {"key": 219, "position": "Software Developer In Security", "company": "Rakuten", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "given a sequence of binary numbers from 1 to n, what is the result of applying the xor operation on each  eg. 0001 xor 0010 xor 0011 xor ....", "answer": ["# Python 3 Program to find\n# XOR of numbers from 1 to n.\ndef computeXOR(n) :\n \n    # Modulus operator are expensive\n    # on most of the computers. n &amp; 3\n    # will be equivalent to n % 4.\n \n    # if n is multiple of 4\n    if n % 4 == 0 :\n        return n\n \n    # If n % 4 gives remainder 1\n    if n % 4 == 1 :\n        return 1\n \n    # If n%4 gives remainder 2\n    if n % 4 == 2 :\n        return n + 1\n \n    # If n%4 gives remainder 3\n    return 0 Less"]}, {"key": 220, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Database related questions on RDBMS and SQL queries", "answer": []}, {"key": 221, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "VIEWNEXT", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Por que te cambias? \nQue funciones realizas? \nDisponibilidad", "answer": []}, {"key": 222, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Technology related questions and domain related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 223, "position": "Software Security Developer", "company": "Helcim", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "what would you do in some specific situations to solve a problem?\nDescribe a past experience when you had succeeded?\netc", "answer": []}, {"key": 224, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Trade Republic", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet", "answer": []}, {"key": 225, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Bitpanda", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "How would you secure a distinct workload in the Cloud?", "answer": []}, {"key": 226, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Security Research Labs", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "whats your name ?\r\nwhat is your current job?\r\nwhat is your specialy skill ?", "answer": ["my name is xxxxx\r\nmy current jobs is xxxxx\r\nmy specialy skill is xxxxx"]}, {"key": 227, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "6 September 2021", "question": "basic of information security\nhow to solve any test case like virus break out", "answer": []}, {"key": 228, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "5 September 2021", "question": "What is your day to day and then go in detail about it.", "answer": ["Explained end to end process I follow."]}, {"key": 229, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ParkNow", "date": "4 September 2021", "question": "Tell us about your experience as security engineer? some questions about python and AWS", "answer": []}, {"key": 230, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Northern Lights Technology Development", "date": "4 September 2021", "question": "What is click jacking ?", "answer": ["Its the most easiest question in web security."]}, {"key": 231, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Nones", "date": "3 September 2021", "question": "is there any vacancy available?", "answer": []}, {"key": 232, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Harness", "date": "2 September 2021", "question": "A real time scenario about the secrets management and how could it be efficiently be resolved was asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 233, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "eClerx", "date": "1 September 2021", "question": "Basics intervuew questions of technology", "answer": []}, {"key": 234, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Silicon Valley Bank", "date": "31 August 2021", "question": "Basics of OWASP\nTools used like-Appscan,Burpsuite\nXSS, CSRF, File upload\nEncryption, Hashing", "answer": []}, {"key": 235, "position": "Devops Security Engineer", "company": "NowPow", "date": "31 August 2021", "question": "How have you worked on securing CI/CD pipelines", "answer": []}, {"key": 236, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Do you have experience with Spring?", "answer": []}, {"key": 237, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Canonical", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Beginning in your high school years, through university and into your career, what have you done that you consider exceptional?\r\nWhy do you want to work for Canonical?\r\nHow are you involved in Open Source software (did you even contributed)?\r\nWhat are your strengths as a software engineer?\r\nLooks like you have been able to gather broad experiences in programming languages - how good would you rate your skills especially in Python and Go?", "answer": []}, {"key": 238, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No questions .. ... .", "answer": []}, {"key": 239, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No Questions ....", "answer": []}, {"key": 240, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No questions with out any questions that could evaluate your skill ,experiences , attitude ..etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 241, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ola", "date": "29 August 2021", "question": "He just asked 50 + questions security terms in 1 hr time kind of definition based.  No scenario based question etc.", "answer": ["I answered what i knew , but was not happy that he has shut his webcam."]}, {"key": 242, "position": "Vehicle Security Engineer", "company": "Nuro", "date": "28 August 2021", "question": "What do you hope to gain out of this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 243, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "27 August 2021", "question": "Take me through your career from the start to present day and how you got to where you are today.", "answer": []}, {"key": 244, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Truveta", "date": "26 August 2021", "question": "Walk through penetration testing scenario the interviewer was describing\r\nWhat is your proudest professional career moment\r\nWhat is a mistake you have made in your career/environment\r\nWhy are you switching jobs", "answer": []}, {"key": 245, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "26 August 2021", "question": "How much do you know about this job position.", "answer": []}, {"key": 246, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "No questions were asked during technical round of interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 247, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "What are the steps and actions to containing a spillage?", "answer": []}, {"key": 248, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "They were very interested in my cloud background given the focus on their cloud family of products, CloudGuard.", "answer": []}, {"key": 249, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AT&T", "date": "24 August 2021", "question": "What is your experience in configuring log collection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 250, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Snyk", "date": "23 August 2021", "question": "Tell me about how you've handled an incident and what you learned from it", "answer": []}, {"key": 251, "position": "Security Network Engineer", "company": "Schroders", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "how do you configure vpc in nexus switches?", "answer": []}, {"key": 252, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Rivian", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "It was more about what my relevant experience was in relation to the job I was applying for.", "answer": []}, {"key": 253, "position": "Automotive Security Developer", "company": "HARMAN", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "1. About working of  SHE Specification  : How SHE Messages M1,M2,M3 are processed by ECU ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 254, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Apex Systems", "date": "19 August 2021", "question": "Typical questions for the field.  They did throw in questions not listed as part of the job description", "answer": ["Described my experiences working in the field"]}, {"key": 255, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "19 August 2021", "question": "Describe the difference in Hashing and Cryptography.", "answer": []}, {"key": 256, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "18 August 2021", "question": "The questions were marked as classified.", "answer": []}, {"key": 257, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "17 August 2021", "question": "Experience with programming and knowledge with algorithms and their use cases is needed.", "answer": []}, {"key": 258, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Klarna", "date": "17 August 2021", "question": "Never asked any questions. Link to a brain teaser quiz. Never got any farther.", "answer": []}, {"key": 259, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zendesk", "date": "15 August 2021", "question": "Those should be some non-necessarily technical questions, but I signed an NDA, so I cannot tell. That is how you keep your company secrets safe after all, right?", "answer": []}, {"key": 260, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Emerson", "date": "15 August 2021", "question": "Q: Please run through your resume and tell me about yourself.", "answer": []}, {"key": 261, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Exabeam", "date": "12 August 2021", "question": "Technical discussion mostly about linux and troubleshooting.", "answer": []}, {"key": 262, "position": "Senior Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "GitHub", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work at GitHub", "answer": []}, {"key": 263, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adobe", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Resume related questions\nSort an array of numbers in words in numerical order", "answer": []}, {"key": 264, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solarisbank", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Are you comfortable with Linux", "answer": []}, {"key": 265, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Pearson", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Explain the difference between a static and non-static inner class.", "answer": []}, {"key": 266, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "10 August 2021", "question": "Read about counting sort in 3 minutes, and implement it based on your understanding.", "answer": []}, {"key": 267, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "HedgeServ", "date": "9 August 2021", "question": "There were no specific technical questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 268, "position": "Client Software Engineer, Security & Cryptography", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "The coding assignment was to design a program that sorts teams for a coding competition", "answer": []}, {"key": 269, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "What is CIA?\nWhat type of IDS did you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 270, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "OCBC Bank", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "Tell us more about the internship project you have done in the final year?", "answer": []}, {"key": 271, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "HSBC", "date": "6 August 2021", "question": "All questions were asked based on my experience and real time case studies. Mainly related to Risk Assessment, Cyber security management, compliance etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 272, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Wikimedia Foundation", "date": "5 August 2021", "question": "Crappy questions that I don't bother to remember", "answer": []}, {"key": 273, "position": "Entry Level Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "General Atomics", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "Cookie cutter interview. Tell me about yourself.", "answer": []}, {"key": 274, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is SQL injection? How do you mitigate it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 275, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is Router vs Switch?", "answer": []}, {"key": 276, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Akamai", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is Content Delivery Network", "answer": ["A CDN (Content Delivery Network) is a highly-distributed platform of servers that helps minimize delays in loading web page content by reducing the physical distance between the server and the user. This helps users around the world view the same high-quality content without slow loading times. Less"]}, {"key": 277, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lindsay Corporation", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "Can you describe what your ideal incident response process would entail?", "answer": []}, {"key": 278, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "3 August 2021", "question": "Questions on Networking and and operating systems.", "answer": []}, {"key": 279, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "Using a script of sudo code how would you create a report from two separate log files to concatenate the files together.", "answer": ["Pull data from log file 1 into a data set.  Pull data from log file 2 into a different data set.  Export results of data set 1 + data set 2. Less"]}, {"key": 280, "position": "Graduate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "How would I react if everyday I had a different task?", "answer": []}, {"key": 281, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Eyeo", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "They asked behavioral questions and technical ones.", "answer": []}, {"key": 282, "position": "Security Services Engineer", "company": "CyberArk", "date": "1 August 2021", "question": "Why I want to work for CyberArk.", "answer": []}, {"key": 283, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HelloFresh", "date": "1 August 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself and your experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 284, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "We expect you to \u201cfail\u201d when you\u2019re new. Describe a time when you failed and what you did after.", "answer": []}, {"key": 285, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "You\u2019re the brand new CISO of a small company and want to secure your endpoints. What is your first step?", "answer": []}, {"key": 286, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "Describe the difference between an IPS, IDS and Firewall; how would you use them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 287, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "we45", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "Some basic assignment on web app pentesting", "answer": []}, {"key": 288, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Citizen (NY)", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "What Products are you familiar with?  Do you have any experience with Google Cloud Engine?", "answer": []}, {"key": 289, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Optimizely", "date": "29 July 2021", "question": "What is your experience around SIEM integration?", "answer": []}, {"key": 290, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Frontline Education", "date": "29 July 2021", "question": "About my work and security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 291, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Skedulo", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "Describe your experience with risk assessment and compliance frameworks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 292, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DISH", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work with Dish? Why are you fit dor this role", "answer": []}, {"key": 293, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wave", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "It started from General Behavioral Questions to technical one which included understanding of DevSecOps, Cloud Security etc. and Team player, Contribution based question", "answer": []}, {"key": 294, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Genesys", "date": "25 July 2021", "question": "Threat Modelling, SAST,DAST,Pentest,\nOWASP top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 295, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tyro Payments", "date": "24 July 2021", "question": "Python Coding exam to perform certain functions", "answer": ["Coding submission"]}, {"key": 296, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sennovate", "date": "24 July 2021", "question": "For my academic project details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 297, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "23 July 2021", "question": "Security, Python, Automation, Detection, Networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 298, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Scenario based questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 299, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Past experience and projects dive deep", "answer": []}, {"key": 300, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Design of security architecture", "answer": []}, {"key": 301, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Design: Given a certain scenario, where and what security controls would you implement?", "answer": []}, {"key": 302, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Projects and past experience questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 303, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Security hardening configurations for operating systems", "answer": []}, {"key": 304, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Email Security features and services for protecting email servers", "answer": []}, {"key": 305, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "What kind of solutions we can use for controlling users access to Cloud Apps", "answer": []}, {"key": 306, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Postman", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "What is this ___ attack and How do you prevent it?", "answer": ["____ -&gt; I was asked about CSRF and XSS. I gave an example while explaining the vulnerability.I spoke about CORS policy, CSRF tokens etc... Less"]}, {"key": 307, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Red Ventures", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "How would you automate security scanning? Describe a role that involved that automation?", "answer": ["Provided about 4 different examples how I was currently conducting automation via Burp, zap, qualys and snyk Less"]}, {"key": 308, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Collective Health", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Why are you looking for a change?", "answer": []}, {"key": 309, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "SpaceX", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "How much do you know about different encryption schemes?", "answer": []}, {"key": 310, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Paycom", "date": "19 July 2021", "question": "Tell me about the OWASP top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 311, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "15 July 2021", "question": "Basic security questions and process \r\nCould not understand most of the terms", "answer": []}, {"key": 312, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "13 July 2021", "question": "What is cybersecurity?\r\nHave you done any relevant job?", "answer": []}, {"key": 313, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "13 July 2021", "question": "Recall a time you failed at something?", "answer": []}, {"key": 314, "position": "Lead Application Security Engineer", "company": "S&P Global", "date": "12 July 2021", "question": "1. They come with python project, asked to identify bugs in python code\r\n2. They run the code and asked to how you enumerate application manually without using 3. nmap, dirbuster nor any automation tool.\r\n4. Explain about Json interoperatable attack\r\n5. Explain about Dependency confusion attack\r\n6. Explain about printspool attack \r\n7. Explain how can get RFI with only having LFI vulnerability in php application\r\n8. Explain about deserialization attack\r\n9. Explain what checks you perform on windows machine to exploit privilege escalation attack\r\n10. How you will perform pivoting attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 315, "position": "Information Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Shaw Industries", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "Asked about the star method and my experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 316, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "Too many tech questions in the get-to-know-you round. That too from googling.", "answer": []}, {"key": 317, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "AceTeam Networks", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "tell me about yourself\ncareer plan\nstrength/weakness\nOSI layers\nProblem and solution on WiFi issues\nWiFi 6 questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 318, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Hands-on knowledge, scenarios, and code reading.", "answer": ["Through experience."]}, {"key": 319, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iOPEX Technologies", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Self introduction, questions regarding our project, have you worked on Iot technology?", "answer": []}, {"key": 320, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Codility with three different questions. 90 min.", "answer": []}, {"key": 321, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Design a calculator and do some coding.", "answer": ["Use a tree"]}, {"key": 322, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "coding an iterator by yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 323, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "7 July 2021", "question": "What are your contributions on your thesis?", "answer": []}, {"key": 324, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "6 July 2021", "question": "Explain XSS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 325, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "6 July 2021", "question": "What is your ideal job like?", "answer": []}, {"key": 326, "position": "Senior Security Engineer, Applications Security", "company": "Genesys", "date": "5 July 2021", "question": "What is Threat Modeling? \r\nWhich Threat Modelling process you follow? Explain How do you perform threat modeling?\r\nWhat is Application Security Architecture Review? Explain  with an example?\r\nApplication Security Code Review Process? What is your approach in code review?\r\nWhat tools you use in Software composition analysis in your organization?\r\nExplain about Security pipelines used in current organization?\r\nWhich code review tools you use? How much level of manual code review you perform? How do you validate the security issues identified in Code Review Tools?\r\nExplain Application Penetration Testing Process?\r\nWhat is your favourite pentesting tool?\r\nHow you came into developement background?\r\nWhich is your favourite development language? What all tools developed by you?\r\nWhat type of common vulnerabilities you encounter when performing security code review?\r\nEncryption and hashing standards?\r\nWhat is cipher suite? How encryption take place in SSL/TLS handshake?\r\nWhat is your approach when performing security assessment on development frameworks?\r\nHave you worked on any SIEM solution? \r\nHave you worked on any Monitoring Solutions?", "answer": []}, {"key": 327, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "4 July 2021", "question": "Describe yourself professionally and why should we hire you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 328, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "BlueCross BlueShield of Tennessee", "date": "3 July 2021", "question": "I am not allowed to discuss the specific questions, but if you look at the job description it will set you up for success.", "answer": ["Just be yourself :-)"]}, {"key": 329, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange Business Services", "date": "2 July 2021", "question": "Basic network basics security basics fortigate", "answer": []}, {"key": 330, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "DISCO", "date": "2 July 2021", "question": "EDR\nNetwork Basics\nSecurity Basics \nScenarios", "answer": []}, {"key": 331, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Amadeus", "date": "1 July 2021", "question": "A question related to scenario, cyber security were covered", "answer": ["Almost all question correct"]}, {"key": 332, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange", "date": "1 July 2021", "question": "Technical related to telecom & endpoint Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 333, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Quotient", "date": "30 June 2021", "question": "Mostly the fundamentals of Networking", "answer": []}, {"key": 334, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forward Networks", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "Deep dive into Technical concepts and Behavioral questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 335, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forward Networks", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "Deep dive into Technical concepts and Behavioral questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 336, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Coinsquare", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "can you describe what CSRF is, and how you would mitigate it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 337, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Coinsquare", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "do you know what the OWASP top 10 are?", "answer": []}, {"key": 338, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "They were pretty standard questions, tailored to the experience on my resume. There were a few things I stumbled on because I was nervous but they were patient and didn't expect me to be a walking encyclopedia. They were more interested in hearing my thought processes, seeing how I approached problems, and seeing how I handled stress.", "answer": []}, {"key": 339, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "28 June 2021", "question": "Describe a OAuth autnorization flow", "answer": []}, {"key": 340, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Acuity Insurance", "date": "28 June 2021", "question": "A common one that seemed to come up a few times was regarding how you view security practices.", "answer": ["Answering it will various things like, least privilege, layered approach, etc opened a lot of discussion and gave me a chance to show how much I knew about broad best practices or my stance on things in the field. Less"]}, {"key": 341, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Iron Mountain", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Mostly asked about my experience based on my resume, and some use cases", "answer": []}, {"key": 342, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Nuveo", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Por qu\u00ea voc\u00ea est\u00e1 saindo da sua \u00faltima empresa?", "answer": []}, {"key": 343, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "CSRF, SOP, CORS, Path Traversal etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 344, "position": "Java Security Developer", "company": "Wipro", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Project Architecture with Rest services", "answer": []}, {"key": 345, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Everlaw", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "What would you do to prevent cross site scripting attacks?", "answer": []}, {"key": 346, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 347, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 348, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "23 June 2021", "question": "Have you ever dealt with an X scenario and how did you manage it? (SOC related questions)", "answer": []}, {"key": 349, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "23 June 2021", "question": "Do you know the MITRE framework?", "answer": []}, {"key": 350, "position": "Senior Network and Security Engineer", "company": "Cirrus Networks", "date": "22 June 2021", "question": "Routing Protocols - BGP\r\nSD-WAN Meraki\r\nSwitch port security", "answer": []}, {"key": 351, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 June 2021", "question": "Can you say something about JSONP?", "answer": []}, {"key": 352, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "How would SOAP calls be tested in Burp?", "answer": []}, {"key": 353, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "What is Java Deserialization? How would you find it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 354, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "What is an XXE injection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 355, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Resideo", "date": "18 June 2021", "question": "all around security and generic concepts of security", "answer": ["was able to answer from what i was already doing"]}, {"key": 356, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Seven Bridges", "date": "18 June 2021", "question": "Explain One of OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities, detecion, explotation and fix.", "answer": []}, {"key": 357, "position": "Sr. Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "The Home Depot", "date": "17 June 2021", "question": "Tell me how you handled a situation where you need to explain a scenario to a non-technical person.\nTell me how you handled your task and was it finished within the deadline.", "answer": []}, {"key": 358, "position": "Security Quality Assurance Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "17 June 2021", "question": "Tell me about your internship experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 359, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 June 2021", "question": "Describe your prior experience/walk me through your resume. \r\nComplete a coding exercise (live).", "answer": []}, {"key": 360, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 June 2021", "question": "Describe your prior experience/walk me through your resume. \r\nComplete a coding exercise (live).", "answer": []}, {"key": 361, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Phillips 66", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "1. Technical difference between Cisco, checkpoint and PaloAlto firewalls.\r\n2. How to configure next Gen firewalls in a network for the first time.", "answer": []}, {"key": 362, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Explain the difference between segmentation and isolation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 363, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Explain what deep packet analysis is/does.", "answer": []}, {"key": 364, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "How to troubleshoot a potential problem in a Linux environment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 365, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Difference between TCP and UDP.", "answer": []}, {"key": 366, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "14 June 2021", "question": "If you had a million dollar to fix a vulnerability class, which one would you choose and why?", "answer": ["Heap based buffer overflows. I\u2019d like to research mitigations that are backward-compatible with the C standard and that don\u2019t require changes to an existing code base. Similar to canaries on the stack. I\u2019d choose that, because this vuln class is frequently exploited and C is not going away any time soon although it\u2019s so old. Less"]}, {"key": 367, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adjust", "date": "12 June 2021", "question": "What are the three qualities you want in a team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 368, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ECS Fin", "date": "12 June 2021", "question": "Questions ranging from web security, DLP, Vulnerability assessment, Network Security, Security engineering, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 369, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "IOVLabs", "date": "11 June 2021", "question": "you need to find vulnerabilities in the code:\n\nDNS lookup code written in Python, .\nAuthentication Code written in typescript , \n\nsql injection question\nquestion about tasks priorities and Agile.\nquestion about password manager.\nquestion about MFA.", "answer": []}, {"key": 370, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Workato", "date": "9 June 2021", "question": "Work experience related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 371, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Cruise", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "I was asked to walk through the thought process of working with a new API I've never seen before. I was presented an actual API, and was asked to free-form pseudocode a call to it.", "answer": ["While sharing my screen, I googled the service, scanned the docs, found relevant calls and began scaffolding pseudocode to auth with the API and pull the requested data. Less"]}, {"key": 372, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "LeQuest", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "tell us about your experience with security", "answer": []}, {"key": 373, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "Projects you did. \nTopics cover almost all areas.\ncryptography, secure coding, owasp top 10, network security (tcp, certificates etc), 1 thread modeling scenario.   \nBehavior question, like if developers refuse to fix the issue etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 374, "position": "Lead Info Security Engineer", "company": "HERE Technologies", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "5 interviews with the same questions over and over, nonsense", "answer": []}, {"key": 375, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Benchling", "date": "7 June 2021", "question": "How to do a basic threat model", "answer": []}, {"key": 376, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ABB", "date": "4 June 2021", "question": "Overall security concepts were asked and good discussion", "answer": ["Good discussion"]}, {"key": 377, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "4 June 2021", "question": "What\u2019s your background and experience with SIEM and SOAR tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 378, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "31 May 2021", "question": "Why Gitlab and what value do you like about the company", "answer": []}, {"key": 379, "position": "Security Compliance Engineer", "company": "PierianDx", "date": "31 May 2021", "question": "How much experience do you have with GPDR?", "answer": []}, {"key": 380, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "The question were mainly on Cross site request forgery.", "answer": []}, {"key": 381, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "2. write a state-machine in verilog", "answer": []}, {"key": 382, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "3.  Synchronous and asynchronous cryptomodule\n4. what is CIA triade", "answer": []}, {"key": 383, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "1. what is secured boot-up?", "answer": []}, {"key": 384, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Eastern Bank", "date": "29 May 2021", "question": "Can you explain the TCP handshake?", "answer": []}, {"key": 385, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Avant", "date": "29 May 2021", "question": "Asked what I knew about Windows endpoints and what I would do to protect them and verify they weren't vulnerable.", "answer": []}, {"key": 386, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Chronus", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "Owasp top10", "answer": []}, {"key": 387, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Chronus", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "Difference between hashing encryption encoding.", "answer": []}, {"key": 388, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Flo Health", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "How would you keep vulnerability metrics up to date?", "answer": []}, {"key": 389, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Collabera", "date": "27 May 2021", "question": "How do you deal with conflict.", "answer": []}, {"key": 390, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "UST", "date": "27 May 2021", "question": "From basics", "answer": []}, {"key": 391, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Plume Design", "date": "26 May 2021", "question": "Questions around my previous work and setting up secure practices for networking team and so on", "answer": []}, {"key": 392, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synopsys", "date": "26 May 2021", "question": "CI / CD definitions, techniques applied during SAST", "answer": []}, {"key": 393, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Credible", "date": "25 May 2021", "question": "Behavioral questions, basic Security Interview questions, \"Do you know how to use kubernetes?\", \"Are you a cloud expert?\", \"How does x work?\", \"Explain y technology\", etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 394, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Credible", "date": "25 May 2021", "question": "Behavioral questions, basic Security Interview questions, \"Do you know how to use kubernetes?\", \"Are you a cloud expert?\", \"How does x work?\", \"Explain y technology\", etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 395, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "23 May 2021", "question": "How would you design a distributed web scraper?", "answer": []}, {"key": 396, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "How do you keep yourself up to date?", "answer": ["I am following some popular websites in cybersecurity, as well as the news."]}, {"key": 397, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "What are your 5 years plans?", "answer": ["I am aiming to get some certifications in my area such as CISSP, beside of this I am looking to get scripting skills such as Phython. Less"]}, {"key": 398, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "What is your most challenging day at work?", "answer": ["It was the day one of my team mate was absent, I handled most of her duties."]}, {"key": 399, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "Why you think this position is a good fit for you?", "answer": ["Based on the job description I found this position is good fit for my technical skills. Less"]}, {"key": 400, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "Why are you leaving your current position?", "answer": ["Ultimately, I\u2019ve learned a lot in my current role, but I\u2019m looking for the next step where I can continue to grow and use the skills I\u2019ve honed at a company I love, and this opportunity seems to be a great fit.\u201d Less"]}, {"key": 401, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "21 May 2021", "question": "Implement the queue class using only stacks.\nCreate a program that generates all valid strings from phone numbers and keypad.", "answer": []}, {"key": 402, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "21 May 2021", "question": "Generic, mostly non-technical questions. Lost my train of thought", "answer": []}, {"key": 403, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "20 May 2021", "question": "when you type in amazon.com on your browser, explain what happens?", "answer": ["Then USA amazon shopping portal website opens up."]}, {"key": 404, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "20 May 2021", "question": "What are some of the problems a workstation may not connect to a network?", "answer": ["Multiple of things can affect the workstation from not connecting. Such as if it was on the domain, is the IP address correct, is the NIC setup the right way, or if the firewall is blocking it from connecting. Less"]}, {"key": 405, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "18 May 2021", "question": "Q: Tell me about a time you made a mistake - how did you handle that?", "answer": []}, {"key": 406, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Faith Technologies Incorporated", "date": "17 May 2021", "question": "How do you set up the devscops model?\nWhat are your recommendations to mature the security posture of the organization?\nHow do you fit into the team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 407, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Blackboard", "date": "16 May 2021", "question": "Tell us more about your background.", "answer": []}, {"key": 408, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "13 May 2021", "question": "Cloud computing", "answer": []}, {"key": 409, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "PrimeRevenue", "date": "13 May 2021", "question": "Describe your coding ability in several languages", "answer": []}, {"key": 410, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "BenchSci", "date": "12 May 2021", "question": "What are the challenges I've seen in security and what did I want to accomplish in the senior security engineer role at Benchschi.", "answer": []}, {"key": 411, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange Business Services", "date": "12 May 2021", "question": "What is the routing looping ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 412, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "BMB", "date": "11 May 2021", "question": "Cisco, F5 , paloalto,forcepoint,ISE,FTD, FMC", "answer": []}, {"key": 413, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Oodle Car Finance", "date": "11 May 2021", "question": "Is there anything in the interview we could have done to attract you more to the company", "answer": []}, {"key": 414, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Clearco", "date": "10 May 2021", "question": "Describe your experience with SOAR platform, how did you set it up and what are the use-cases?", "answer": []}, {"key": 415, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "MindGeek", "date": "9 May 2021", "question": "Do you have experience with container security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 416, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "9 May 2021", "question": "I got many questions about firewalls, differences between multiple firewall types and IPS/IDS, and other networking-related questions. The Engineer holding my technical interview seemed rather a friendly senior colleague assessing my level of knowledge than someone judging me. There was no technical test for this role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 417, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "Why do you want to leave your current role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 418, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "What are you looking for in this role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 419, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in next 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 420, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "OWASP top 10, Remediation techniques and latest vulnerability trend", "answer": []}, {"key": 421, "position": "Info Security Engineer", "company": "Wells Fargo", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "Explain data level encryption.\nWhat is PKI and certificate management.", "answer": []}, {"key": 422, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Informatica", "date": "6 May 2021", "question": "Describe a situation from past work experience which was difficult .", "answer": []}, {"key": 423, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "6 May 2021", "question": "How would you describe a good manager you had worked with in the past?", "answer": []}, {"key": 424, "position": "Security Consulting Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "5 May 2021", "question": "Penetration Testing of web applications, APIs and thick client applications, threat modelling, cloud security, loggingand monitoring, Patching", "answer": []}, {"key": 425, "position": "Senior Security Site Reliability Engineer", "company": "Arkose Labs", "date": "4 May 2021", "question": "What's important to lead the team?", "answer": ["To be able to relate to the engineers at a level that makes feel safe and secure. Less"]}, {"key": 426, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synopsys", "date": "1 May 2021", "question": "questions were related to networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 427, "position": "AWS Security Engineer", "company": "LetsGetChecked", "date": "30 April 2021", "question": "How would you configure security tooling within an AWS account?", "answer": []}, {"key": 428, "position": "Associate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Immersive Labs", "date": "30 April 2021", "question": "Interactive assignment for technical fundamentals", "answer": []}, {"key": 429, "position": "Associate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Immersive Labs", "date": "30 April 2021", "question": "Interactive assignment for technical fundamentals", "answer": []}, {"key": 430, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DoorDash", "date": "29 April 2021", "question": "typical first interview questions. Asked about my back ground and experience in certain areas. Nothing too technical.", "answer": []}, {"key": 431, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ClarionDoor", "date": "29 April 2021", "question": "1. talk about your network security project\n2. talk about AES-ECB, what is the padding attack?\n3. If you have a web server, what ports will you open?\n4. What courses related to security did you have?\n5. How do you secure a web sever on AWS?", "answer": []}, {"key": 432, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "29 April 2021", "question": "where u wanna see yourself in next 3-5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 433, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Fortress Information Security", "date": "28 April 2021", "question": "What are the differences and why would you use one set of analysis tools over the other.", "answer": []}, {"key": 434, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "28 April 2021", "question": "Encryption\nAWS \nScenario-based questions\nCoding\nUnderstanding of Technology", "answer": []}, {"key": 435, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "28 April 2021", "question": "what have you learnt in your cybersecurity courses?", "answer": ["I explained brief info about my CEH course and CPTE course."]}, {"key": 436, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Motley Fool", "date": "26 April 2021", "question": "Which specific security systems did you personally implement? \nWhich specific security systems did you personally  manage?\nWhat challenges have you encountered in your prior security work and how did you overcome them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 437, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "DataRemote", "date": "26 April 2021", "question": "technical and personal, nothing out of the ordinary", "answer": []}, {"key": 438, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Riot Games", "date": "26 April 2021", "question": "Q) (After 7 rounds of interview) Would you be able to take another round since the interviewer missed covering an area?", "answer": ["Should have gone with \"I am sorry! At this point, I want to discontinue the interview process\". Less"]}, {"key": 439, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "23 April 2021", "question": "Asked about my  experience and then specifics on networking", "answer": []}, {"key": 440, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ITSC Secure Solutions", "date": "23 April 2021", "question": "They talked a lot about culture and how important it was and asked how culture plays a role in previous positions.  They also asked about long term goals and aspirations, and asked about your areas of passion.  They really seemed focused on finding the right person, not just a person that fits the job description.", "answer": []}, {"key": 441, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "UST", "date": "23 April 2021", "question": "SIEM tool that I worked with", "answer": ["Qradar , arcsight"]}, {"key": 442, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "N26", "date": "23 April 2021", "question": "Not much was asked, most of the time was spent arguing (see above).", "answer": []}, {"key": 443, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "22 April 2021", "question": "What are the layers of the OSI model and what do they do", "answer": []}, {"key": 444, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "TuSimple", "date": "21 April 2021", "question": "General questions about my resume.\r\nTechnical questions covering various fields.", "answer": []}, {"key": 445, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ankura", "date": "21 April 2021", "question": "Tell me about your resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 446, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer (Professional Services)", "company": "Threat Stack", "date": "20 April 2021", "question": "Some very basic networking questions (standard ports for certain activities) as well as some basic command line commands (Windows/Linux) for the screening call.", "answer": []}, {"key": 447, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "20 April 2021", "question": "Questions mostly what i have written in my resume and little technical question regarding internet connection", "answer": []}, {"key": 448, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Abarca", "date": "19 April 2021", "question": "What is a wrong impression people have gotten from you and how have you proved them wrong?", "answer": []}, {"key": 449, "position": "Senior Security Engineer, Cloud &amp;Amp; Infrastructure", "company": "Rokt", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "It\u2019s making me enter a question here.", "answer": []}, {"key": 450, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Orange", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "What's your day-to-day work. It's more of an open-ended question to get to know your experience, ...etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 451, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Ingenicomm", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "Typical interview questions. What are you looking for and why?", "answer": []}, {"key": 452, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "OutSystems", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "What is the key difference in doing security for cloud and On-Prem", "answer": []}, {"key": 453, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "OutSystems", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "What is the difference in doing security in Cloud and On-Prem.?", "answer": []}, {"key": 454, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Pentagon System and Services", "date": "16 April 2021", "question": "Security topics like Network security fundamentals, firewall topologies and some basic concept of Routing and Switching", "answer": []}, {"key": 455, "position": "Security Incident Response Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "15 April 2021", "question": "Why are you interested in this role? How much do you know about Twitch? A couple scenario questions about how I would approach a security incident.", "answer": []}, {"key": 456, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Mission Operations and Services", "date": "15 April 2021", "question": "Background technologies used in security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 457, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory", "date": "13 April 2021", "question": "General questions about prior experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 458, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "PayPay", "date": "13 April 2021", "question": "OpenSSL , Docker & Kubernetes, Scenario based questions, Most challenging task faced in my Security perspective career etc etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 459, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ShorePoint", "date": "12 April 2021", "question": "Scenario-based questions for penetration testing/red teaming", "answer": ["With a scenario-based answer borne from years of experience in this field"]}, {"key": 460, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ShorePoint", "date": "12 April 2021", "question": "Scenario-based questions for penetration testing/red teaming", "answer": []}, {"key": 461, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Included Health", "date": "12 April 2021", "question": "Can you provide some insight into some workplace challenges you have managed and describe how you handled or solved these issues?", "answer": []}, {"key": 462, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "DNC", "date": "11 April 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself and how did you come to apply for this position with DNC.", "answer": []}, {"key": 463, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "DNC", "date": "11 April 2021", "question": "Various situational questions and how would I handle or what would be my suggestion to improve.", "answer": []}, {"key": 464, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ABB", "date": "11 April 2021", "question": "How IPS is working on span port", "answer": []}, {"key": 465, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Marshall Wace North America", "date": "11 April 2021", "question": "Very broad range of topics, testing breadth of knowledge as well as depth.", "answer": []}, {"key": 466, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Lincoln Financial Group", "date": "10 April 2021", "question": "Essentially was asked to detail up my previous positions", "answer": []}, {"key": 467, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "WhiteHat Security", "date": "9 April 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work for Whitehat?", "answer": []}, {"key": 468, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "WhiteHat Security", "date": "9 April 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work for Whitehat?", "answer": []}, {"key": 469, "position": "Lead Application Security Engineer", "company": "Aptible", "date": "8 April 2021", "question": "Tell me about a time when you received tough/critical feedback.", "answer": []}, {"key": 470, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Alethe Consulting", "date": "8 April 2021", "question": "On which OEM's do you have hand's on experies", "answer": ["Multi vendor OEM like checkpoint , Palo alto , F5 , Juniper PSA , Cisco ISE and Cisco Router Less"]}, {"key": 471, "position": "Graduate - Software, Platform Or Security Engineer", "company": "BP", "date": "8 April 2021", "question": "Asked to design a UI based on a given specification", "answer": []}, {"key": 472, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Acumen Security", "date": "8 April 2021", "question": "What my home setup was to keep up with penetration testing.", "answer": []}, {"key": 473, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PrudentRx", "date": "7 April 2021", "question": "What technologies I have worked on in the past", "answer": []}, {"key": 474, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Communications", "date": "6 April 2021", "question": "what is Vpn and how to install hotfix in checkpoint", "answer": []}, {"key": 475, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "6 April 2021", "question": "Normal technical question ..some coding and normal HR questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 476, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "6 April 2021", "question": "What challenges did you face in previous jobs and how did you overcome them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 477, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ManTech", "date": "5 April 2021", "question": "What was my biggest weakness?", "answer": ["Take on too many tasks at once without finishing one."]}, {"key": 478, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "5 April 2021", "question": "Explain in detail different  Linux commands, network architecture, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 479, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "5 April 2021", "question": "Generic questions, asking about products and solutions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 480, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deriv.com", "date": "4 April 2021", "question": "The questions were general security questions, for example, What is SQLi and types, What tools used for pen-testing (SQLmap, Metasploit ...), CIA triad, HTTPs .....", "answer": []}, {"key": 481, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deriv.com", "date": "4 April 2021", "question": "The questions were general security questions, for example, What is SQLi and types, What tools used for pen-testing (SQLmap, Metasploit ...), CIA triad, HTTPs .....", "answer": []}, {"key": 482, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deriv.com", "date": "4 April 2021", "question": "The questions were general security questions, for example, What is SQLi and types, What tools used for pen-testing (SQLmap, Metasploit ...), CIA triad, HTTPs .....", "answer": []}, {"key": 483, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deriv.com", "date": "4 April 2021", "question": "The questions were general security questions, for example, What is SQLi and types, What tools used for pen-testing (SQLmap, Metasploit ...), CIA triad, HTTPs .....", "answer": []}, {"key": 484, "position": "Data Security Engineer", "company": "Block", "date": "3 April 2021", "question": "It was on of the leetcode hard design problems.", "answer": []}, {"key": 485, "position": "Presales Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Diyar United", "date": "2 April 2021", "question": "If the white board in your office was filled with information, would you think of it and give it a thought or ignore it and assume it's not your business?", "answer": []}, {"key": 486, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Aras", "date": "1 April 2021", "question": "Technical questions about my level of experience with various tools i.e. SIEM, IDS/IPS, NGFW, Azure AD.", "answer": []}, {"key": 487, "position": "Senior Cloud Network Security Engineer", "company": "Netskope", "date": "30 March 2021", "question": "Networking basics\nNetworking troubleshooting\nNetwork Design\nNetwork Security fundamentals\nNetwork Security scenarios\nTechnical deep dive into NG firewalls, Proxies, Load Balancers & VPNs", "answer": []}, {"key": 488, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "SonarSource", "date": "30 March 2021", "question": "Had to prepare 20 minutes technical presentation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 489, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "30 March 2021", "question": "How will you Connect to France exchange to your new startup?", "answer": []}, {"key": 490, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "29 March 2021", "question": "What is a route reflector for?", "answer": []}, {"key": 491, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "28 March 2021", "question": "Why did I finish college long enough", "answer": ["Due to financial needs"]}, {"key": 492, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Abhijeet Group", "date": "26 March 2021", "question": "They asked me about a conflict situation", "answer": []}, {"key": 493, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Vertafore", "date": "26 March 2021", "question": "What made you want to apply at Vertafore?", "answer": []}, {"key": 494, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Abbott", "date": "26 March 2021", "question": "What is asymmetric encryption? Symmetric encryption? How do you send the key to the other end user? What is SSH ? What is a shell? Difference of Nist and Cybersecurity Framework?", "answer": ["Just do a google search of the most basic Cybersecurity questions"]}, {"key": 495, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "emarsys", "date": "26 March 2021", "question": "Look at our GitHub what would you suggest to improve", "answer": []}, {"key": 496, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Deloitte", "date": "25 March 2021", "question": "how is Technical security managed", "answer": ["Technically"]}, {"key": 497, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tractive", "date": "25 March 2021", "question": "What is the CIA triad", "answer": []}, {"key": 498, "position": "IT system security engineer", "company": "SAP NS2", "date": "24 March 2021", "question": "It was more of a conversational interview", "answer": ["Tell me about your self"]}, {"key": 499, "position": "Technical Support Engineer Cyber Security", "company": "BreachLock", "date": "24 March 2021", "question": "I reviewed your application for our Technical Support Engineer - Cyber Security job and am impressed with your background. I\u2019d like to schedule a call with you to discuss your experience. Can you book a call.", "answer": []}, {"key": 500, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BambooHR", "date": "23 March 2021", "question": "How would you set up an email server?", "answer": []}, {"key": 501, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "23 March 2021", "question": "What will you do to if you handle a customer that knows a little to nothing about technology?", "answer": ["I would place myself in their place and guide/inform them carefully and clearly. And always put in your mind that they have very little knowledge about technology. Less"]}, {"key": 502, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "SPN Solutions", "date": "22 March 2021", "question": "What is your experience with scanning?", "answer": []}, {"key": 503, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "OWASP Top-10 and mitigations\nBasic networking protocols\nThreat Modelling scenarios\nBasic security fundamentals\nApplication security basics\nScenario based security questions\n\nBehavioral questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 504, "position": "Junior cloud security engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "difference between http and https? I applied for it online then I was appointed for an interview. It was occured via Amazon Chime that smiliar to zoom, MS team. I took an hour including technical questions. some questions about generic security and network questions. they were not about cloud aws questions. SAML, SSO, ssl/tls, dns, routing, certficate revocation, etc", "answer": ["port 80 (http) is not secure, while 443 https is secure since ssl/tls is deployed. Less"]}, {"key": 505, "position": "Junior cloud security engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "What is CIA ? give samples? why is it important? I applied for it online then I was appointed for an interview. It was occured via Amazon Chime that smiliar to zoom, MS team. I took an hour including technical questions. some questions about generic security and network questions. they were not about cloud aws questions. SAML, SSO, ssl/tls, dns, routing, certficate revocation, etc", "answer": ["- confidentially (non-disclosure, encryption), Integrity(hashing-hmac)  and availabitity(resilent DDoS attack) Less"]}, {"key": 506, "position": "Junior cloud security engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "certificate revocation. how to check it? why is it required, or fuction?", "answer": ["there are 2 types of revocation that is dependent on your webbrowser process. please google it. Less"]}, {"key": 507, "position": "Junior cloud security engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "How does it work when I type www.amazon.com? how does packets go over the internet?", "answer": []}, {"key": 508, "position": "Junior cloud security engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 March 2021", "question": "How does ssl/tls work? How about certification. CA authority etc.I applied for it online then I was appointed for an interview. It was occured via Amazon Chime that smiliar to zoom, MS team. I took an hour including technical questions. some questions about generic security and network questions. they were not about cloud aws questions. SAML, SSO, ssl/tls, dns, routing, certficate revocation, etc", "answer": ["check diffie hellman process. be familar with public private key infrastructure"]}, {"key": 509, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Microland", "date": "20 March 2021", "question": "It was technical like vss and firewall", "answer": ["yes good"]}, {"key": 510, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Penn State", "date": "19 March 2021", "question": "Owasp top 10, csa, firewalls", "answer": ["Correxrly"]}, {"key": 511, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Milhouse Engineering & Construction", "date": "19 March 2021", "question": "What tools do you recommend for x?", "answer": []}, {"key": 512, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GitHub", "date": "18 March 2021", "question": "\"Tell me about a time you developed a project and how far you worked with that project throughout it's lifecycle\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 513, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Haven Technologies", "date": "17 March 2021", "question": "A) Security tools I worked with in the past", "answer": []}, {"key": 514, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "16 March 2021", "question": "technology and web fundamentals including cloud", "answer": []}, {"key": 515, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "16 March 2021", "question": "If I know the difference between pentesting and red teaming.\nExperience with web app testing tools.\nScripting/coding experience (in-depth, we actively analyzed code in an exercise)\nBasic security features and capabilities of PC (I said I was not Mac-heavy in experience)\nAttack vectors such as XSS, CSRF, injection, RFI, etc.\nReporting and findings\nCommunication ability and style (verbally and written)", "answer": []}, {"key": 516, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "16 March 2021", "question": "Why I wanted to work for Zoom specifically.", "answer": ["I did my research to make sure the job I was seeking aligned with my values and professional growth goals. I looked in to the CEO, I read about culture and other employee experiences, I researched work/life balance. I also read about the company's revenue and growth metrics and other business's commentaries on the work they do here. I made sure this was a place I would belong and wanted to belong. I also, since I work in information security, researched their outlook and buy-in to security to see if my job is an important asset to the company or if I'd be fighting an uphill battle everyday to prove the worth fo the work I do. Security is obviously a top priority for everyone as Zoom, so it was a match made in infosec heaven. Less"]}, {"key": 517, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Indra", "date": "16 March 2021", "question": "Experiencia laboral previa, conocimientos sobre tecnolog\u00edas, tareas y responsabilidades del puesto ofrecido", "answer": []}, {"key": 518, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Bluestaq", "date": "15 March 2021", "question": "A less serious interview question I was asked was Marvel or DC?", "answer": ["There is no right answer to this question of course but I chose Marvel."]}, {"key": 519, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Akamai", "date": "14 March 2021", "question": "Describe HTTP 1.2 and 2.0", "answer": []}, {"key": 520, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Akamai", "date": "14 March 2021", "question": "What is the ssl traffic?", "answer": []}, {"key": 521, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flywire", "date": "12 March 2021", "question": "They asked no typical interview questions. They basically just asked for advice on IR, CTI, SecOps tooling and processes but framed the questions like it was an interview.", "answer": []}, {"key": 522, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Very Good Security", "date": "12 March 2021", "question": "Explain why you want to work at VGS", "answer": []}, {"key": 523, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Threat Stack", "date": "12 March 2021", "question": "During one interview, we discussed various cyber breaches. One of the case studies discussed was the breach of Maersk. Based on what was known now, the interviewer wanted to know what I would had done differently to mitigate and recover from said breach.", "answer": []}, {"key": 524, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Threat Stack", "date": "12 March 2021", "question": "During one interview, we discussed various cyber breaches. One of the case studies discussed was the breach of Maersk. Based on what was known now the interviewer wanted to know what I would had done differently to mitigate and recover from said breach.", "answer": []}, {"key": 525, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "recharge.com", "date": "11 March 2021", "question": "Tell us about your experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 526, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "11 March 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 527, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MoneyLion", "date": "11 March 2021", "question": "About myself and what I have done previously", "answer": []}, {"key": 528, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Microland", "date": "10 March 2021", "question": "Basic networking question, basic security question", "answer": []}, {"key": 529, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Chan Zuckerberg Initiative", "date": "9 March 2021", "question": "How would you optimize front end web graphics?", "answer": []}, {"key": 530, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Chan Zuckerberg Initiative", "date": "9 March 2021", "question": "How would you implement CSP at scale?", "answer": []}, {"key": 531, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "8 March 2021", "question": "I am not disclosing this.", "answer": []}, {"key": 532, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Netpoleon Solutions", "date": "8 March 2021", "question": "What do you vision yourself to be in 5 years time?", "answer": []}, {"key": 533, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 March 2021", "question": "What are some of your favorite persistence mechanisms for macOS?", "answer": []}, {"key": 534, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Los Alamos National Laboratory", "date": "8 March 2021", "question": "What are the steps in RMF.", "answer": ["I outlined the process of RMF lifecycle"]}, {"key": 535, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Alight Solutions", "date": "6 March 2021", "question": "OSI models\nBasic CCNA \nRouting protocols and AD", "answer": []}, {"key": 536, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "6 March 2021", "question": "- Application security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 537, "position": "Principal Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "5 March 2021", "question": "n/a", "answer": []}, {"key": 538, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Fortinet", "date": "5 March 2021", "question": "Tell me something about yourself\r\nWhy Fortinet", "answer": []}, {"key": 539, "position": "Security Quality Assurance Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "4 March 2021", "question": "All questions around your resume.\r\nTechnical and Behavioral questions. \r\nQuestions are asked on what you say at the interview.\r\nThey ask you more and more around your answers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 540, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "4 March 2021", "question": "The questions during the interview were related to the job role and my experience.  They mostly dived into remediating vulnerabilities and lot of follow up questions with different business requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 541, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "4 March 2021", "question": "What are your threat modeling experiences?", "answer": []}, {"key": 542, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "CSS Corporation", "date": "3 March 2021", "question": "Basic English reading, writing and listening test in the first round.", "answer": []}, {"key": 543, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PayPal", "date": "3 March 2021", "question": "Whats is HA setup in Firewall?\nHow do you setup a BGP?\nwhat is TCP flag  ?\nHow to permit a port on firewall?\nHow to filter the BGP traffic path?\nHow to mitigate DDos attacks?\nHow SSL works?\nHow IPsec works ?\nwhat is AH and ESP ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 544, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Krishna Consultants", "date": "2 March 2021", "question": "Please explain security architecture  of best practices", "answer": ["Good"]}, {"key": 545, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "28 February 2021", "question": "Scenario based and technical depth", "answer": []}, {"key": 546, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "28 February 2021", "question": "None", "answer": []}, {"key": 547, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "Amazon", "date": "26 February 2021", "question": "Technical:\r\nHashing vs. Encryption?\r\nSymmetric vs Asymmetric? Examples of each?\r\nOWASP Top 10 and how to prevent them\r\nHashing scenario problem\r\nAuthentication scenario problem\r\nSession management scenario problem (CSRF)\r\nCertificate Authority \r\nDNS\r\nRecent hacks/news around cybersecurity\r\n\r\nBehavioral: \r\nWhy Amazon?\r\nTell me about a goal and the steps you took the accomplish\r\nTell me about a time you went through a personal obstacle or challenge\r\nTell me about your favorite project\r\nTell me about a time when you took on something you weren\u2019t required to do", "answer": []}, {"key": 548, "position": "Security Research Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "26 February 2021", "question": "How would you go about identifying a string with balanced parentheses.", "answer": ["Use a stack to load and deload parentheses pairs."]}, {"key": 549, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "6sense", "date": "26 February 2021", "question": "Scenario based questions about OWASP security. Mitigations. AWS environments. improvements on overall security structure. SSDLC process, tools specific questions on implementations. DevsecOps. What happens if you type google in the browser and the possible threats.", "answer": []}, {"key": 550, "position": "Cyber-Security Engineer | Pen Tester", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "25 February 2021", "question": "What is the command-line option to set the source port for a nmap scan?", "answer": ["-g or --source-port"]}, {"key": 551, "position": "Security Research Engineer", "company": "SecPod Technologies", "date": "24 February 2021", "question": "Round 1\r\nEasy security related questions. Uses of stack. Code for infix to postfix. Regex for identifying CVE numbers\r\n\r\nRound 2\r\nDifference between TCP and UDP. Which to use where. Other easy vulnerability related questions.\r\n\r\nRound 3\r\nHR round. General inquiry into life and future plans.\r\n\r\nRound 4\r\nMore or less of round 3. Most difficult problem faced. Why security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 552, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Redfin", "date": "23 February 2021", "question": "Coding interview was the focus.", "answer": []}, {"key": 553, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "23 February 2021", "question": "- In my case it was more about coding, code review and situational questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 554, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "N26", "date": "23 February 2021", "question": "CTF\r\nDescribe how will you handle when a developer pushes back for security fixes", "answer": []}, {"key": 555, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Auxilium Pharmaceuticals", "date": "23 February 2021", "question": "what is a CSRF and SSRF?", "answer": []}, {"key": 556, "position": "Cyber Security Threat Engineer", "company": "Garmin", "date": "23 February 2021", "question": "Scenarios, what happens if someone breaks into the site and so on.", "answer": []}, {"key": 557, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "22 February 2021", "question": "Explain OWSAP Top 10 and VPN connection", "answer": []}, {"key": 558, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Capgemini", "date": "22 February 2021", "question": "Any reason you are changing your job shorttime , we saw your profile very recently you are looking new job", "answer": []}, {"key": 559, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "22 February 2021", "question": "Describe all the mechanisms you would use to find passwords on a powered off device.", "answer": []}, {"key": 560, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Invictus International Consulting", "date": "22 February 2021", "question": "RMF was the main focus /  very technical /", "answer": ["I answered extremely well     (the internal guy got the job)  just be aware of the scenario interview fodder.  That appears to be a part of their HR Game Less"]}, {"key": 561, "position": "Security Software Developer COOP", "company": "Nokia", "date": "20 February 2021", "question": "Can not disclose the questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 562, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "19 February 2021", "question": "The most interesting questions were walking them through my process of performing web and mobile application assessments, as well as walking them through exploiting several CVEs I had. \nFinally there was some C and python code review, looking for standard bugs in C (Largely memory corruption related) and some web specific logic bugs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 563, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "19 February 2021", "question": "I was asked to describe my background and experience how it was relevant to the job.", "answer": []}, {"key": 564, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Nuveo", "date": "18 February 2021", "question": "Descreva a sua familiaridade com tecnologias de nuvem.", "answer": []}, {"key": 565, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Wilson Sonsini Goodrich & Rosati", "date": "17 February 2021", "question": "What type of technologies do you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 566, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Oscar Health", "date": "16 February 2021", "question": "Q. Basic Questions that were related to my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 567, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amount", "date": "16 February 2021", "question": "Q. Mostly questions related to my resume\r\nQ. Difference between XSS and CSRF?\r\nQ. Why you want to make the move?", "answer": []}, {"key": 568, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AppFolio", "date": "16 February 2021", "question": "Recruiter Call:\r\n\r\nQ. Tell me about yourself\r\nQ. About the company\r\nQ. Your past experience\r\n\r\nHiring Manager Round:\r\n\r\nQ. All questions were related to the tools and technologies that I mentioned on my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 569, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Procore Technologies", "date": "16 February 2021", "question": "What do the company values mean to you, and give an example when you had to apply one or all of them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 570, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "16 February 2021", "question": "Top 10 OWASP vulnerabilities\nThreat\nRisk \nRemediation", "answer": []}, {"key": 571, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "15 February 2021", "question": "Q. security best practises,  behavioral questions in third round", "answer": []}, {"key": 572, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "15 February 2021", "question": "Describe a time where you were getting pressure from a customer.", "answer": []}, {"key": 573, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "14 February 2021", "question": "Pour quoi tu penses faire un changement dans ta carri\u00e8re professionnelle ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 574, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intercom", "date": "13 February 2021", "question": "I was rejected after the take-home test submission.", "answer": []}, {"key": 575, "position": "Network Data &amp; Security Engineer- Executive- Service Operations", "company": "Macquarie Group", "date": "13 February 2021", "question": "based on ospf bgp f5 asa / checkpoint / paloalto firewalls", "answer": ["aas per my experience"]}, {"key": 576, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "12 February 2021", "question": "Various questions on the platform that I'll be handling and managing, as well as design questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 577, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PayPay", "date": "12 February 2021", "question": "They were looking to get 90 minutes of free consulting on issues they had no ideas how to resolve. I am happy I was not offered a position as I would of not liked to work with them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 578, "position": "IT Operations and Security Engineer", "company": "Arabesque ", "date": "12 February 2021", "question": "How to do you apply an app to Microsoft InTune", "answer": ["Azure Portal &gt; Client Apps &gt; Add"]}, {"key": 579, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "11 February 2021", "question": "tell me about what your concentration", "answer": []}, {"key": 580, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "11 February 2021", "question": "Was asked to design an enterprise system architecture that would span multiple cloud providers and regions, formally document it, then be prepared to present it for a panel interview.", "answer": ["The take-home assignment was absurd and I pursued other options."]}, {"key": 581, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "11 February 2021", "question": "Tell about a time that you had a big impact on a project.", "answer": []}, {"key": 582, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Atos", "date": "11 February 2021", "question": "How many years have you been with your current employer?", "answer": ["I responded with a number describing months and years."]}, {"key": 583, "position": "Product Security Engineer PSIRT", "company": "Rockwell Automation", "date": "11 February 2021", "question": "Technical questions around web app vulnerabilities, cryptography.\nStandard behavioral questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 584, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "10 February 2021", "question": "Why use TLS\r\nWhy Google uses TLS", "answer": []}, {"key": 585, "position": "IT Operations and Security Engineer", "company": "Arabesque ", "date": "9 February 2021", "question": "Do you have any academic qualifications, as I do not see any on your C.V.", "answer": ["Is this a pre-requisite in order perform this role? As I find that question to be somewhat elitist. Less"]}, {"key": 586, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Amazon", "date": "8 February 2021", "question": "Protocols,Attack Vectors ,Cryptography,Penetration Testing, and Network Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 587, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "ByteDance", "date": "8 February 2021", "question": "SQL  injection\nICMP attack\nXML \nVlan routing\nWifi based\nFirewall\nBGP\nSplunk", "answer": []}, {"key": 588, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Binance", "date": "7 February 2021", "question": "Algorithm: Time and Space Complexity for common algorithms\r\nSecurity: Overall pen testing methodology, common security issues, fixing security issues, mobile security fundamentals.", "answer": []}, {"key": 589, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "The Home Depot", "date": "6 February 2021", "question": "Technical Questions are all product related as their Teams specialize in product placements.\n\nManagement meeting: Tell me about a hardship you had to overcome with underperforming team members and how did you manage the situation? What was the outcome, and what did you do to help the person?", "answer": []}, {"key": 590, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "PayPal", "date": "5 February 2021", "question": "Asked mostly about experiences on my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 591, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "5 February 2021", "question": "Questions on Splunk, Linux, and Python", "answer": []}, {"key": 592, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NTT Ltd.", "date": "4 February 2021", "question": "Explaining the ARP protocol in detail.", "answer": []}, {"key": 593, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "3 February 2021", "question": "What makes u to apply to company and the position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 594, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "3 February 2021", "question": "If you checked out the company values and what u think", "answer": []}, {"key": 595, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "3 February 2021", "question": "Describe work experience that\u2019s relevant?", "answer": []}, {"key": 596, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Thought Machine", "date": "2 February 2021", "question": "One string parsing algorithms question of medium difficulty.", "answer": []}, {"key": 597, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Thought Machine", "date": "2 February 2021", "question": "How do you keep up to date with the latest security developments? What are your news sources?", "answer": []}, {"key": 598, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Thought Machine", "date": "2 February 2021", "question": "What steps would you take to secure an application running on Kubernetes, at each level?", "answer": []}, {"key": 599, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "1 February 2021", "question": "Whether you felt  anytime that the domain you are in is not your cup of tea.", "answer": []}, {"key": 600, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Armory", "date": "1 February 2021", "question": "explain about Server side request forgery", "answer": []}, {"key": 601, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "1 February 2021", "question": "How key is used to sign the msg?", "answer": ["private key"]}, {"key": 602, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "31 January 2021", "question": "Its purely based on technical questions with some programming.", "answer": []}, {"key": 603, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "31 January 2021", "question": "Present a project/presentation that is relevant to the job", "answer": []}, {"key": 604, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Balyasny Asset Management", "date": "29 January 2021", "question": "We didn't even get to the interview questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 605, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ByteDance", "date": "29 January 2021", "question": "Introduce yourself (No follow up questions on this part) \nwhat is SQL injection attack?\nwhat is XSS ?\nwhat is ping attack ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 606, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Subex", "date": "29 January 2021", "question": "Wen application security, Networking, Malware analysis", "answer": []}, {"key": 607, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Booking.com", "date": "28 January 2021", "question": "What are you doing as an App Sec engineer in your company?", "answer": []}, {"key": 608, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Booking.com", "date": "28 January 2021", "question": "Your background in App Sec", "answer": []}, {"key": 609, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceTitan", "date": "28 January 2021", "question": "Explain SQL Injection, CSRF, how to mitigate SQLi, XSRF", "answer": []}, {"key": 610, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 January 2021", "question": "Know your basics!! Just prepare all you can.", "answer": []}, {"key": 611, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 January 2021", "question": "write a port scanner in any language of your choosing", "answer": []}, {"key": 612, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lavelle Networks", "date": "27 January 2021", "question": "Q- What are different layers in ISO OSI model", "answer": []}, {"key": 613, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flatiron Health", "date": "26 January 2021", "question": "Past experience and background information.", "answer": []}, {"key": 614, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "26 January 2021", "question": "Look up default Security questions on the internet and they will be very close.   Know basic networking and how to configure firewalls.  Know how to work with Qradar, and nessus.", "answer": ["All questions we situational, no way to cram for it.  Just get good experience.  If you dont have it, you wont get a job here. Less"]}, {"key": 615, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "25 January 2021", "question": "What is your biggest strength?", "answer": ["work ethic"]}, {"key": 616, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "25 January 2021", "question": "-describe recursion to a small child.\n-what is the biggest project you ever did? how many lines approximately?\n-what programming languages do you prefer?", "answer": []}, {"key": 617, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datto ", "date": "24 January 2021", "question": "What is a deserialization vulnerability and how do you prevent it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 618, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NCR", "date": "23 January 2021", "question": "What is your reason to join NCR over other companies?", "answer": ["My passion is cyber security and that's simple reason to join a core cyber security organization. The simple answer and my resume was enough for HR o judge my passion to join the profile. Less"]}, {"key": 619, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "TikTok", "date": "22 January 2021", "question": "Merge two lowest duplicates in an array until none left.", "answer": []}, {"key": 620, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Chime", "date": "22 January 2021", "question": "What\u2019s your experience with container/Kubernetes security?\r\n\r\nDescribe several [cloud service] log types and what kind of information they provide.\r\n\r\nWhich security systems would you plan to work on first if hired?", "answer": ["The key in these questions is to cover the fundamentals, and be ready for the back-and-forth with the interviewer.\r\n\r\n\r\nMight be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Chime or ex-Chime  Security Engineer experts on Prepfully? They give real-world practice and guidance, which is pretty helpful.\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 621, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "ICE Mortgage Technology", "date": "22 January 2021", "question": "Describe the differences between Terraform and Cloudformation", "answer": []}, {"key": 622, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Redfin", "date": "22 January 2021", "question": "The OSI 7 layers of the internet.", "answer": []}, {"key": 623, "position": "IT Systems Security Engineer", "company": "BAE Systems USA", "date": "21 January 2021", "question": "What are your strongest skillsets?", "answer": []}, {"key": 624, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Mastercard", "date": "21 January 2021", "question": "Threat Modeling, standard security questions. Some behavioral questions on how you dealt with senior management and communicated risk.", "answer": []}, {"key": 625, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "20 January 2021", "question": "How were you able to solve conflicts in your group?", "answer": []}, {"key": 626, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adarma", "date": "20 January 2021", "question": "Which encryption algorithm to use for very large pieces of data", "answer": ["One with low complexity"]}, {"key": 627, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BreachLock", "date": "20 January 2021", "question": "describe the hardest situation you faced", "answer": []}, {"key": 628, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "20 January 2021", "question": "1. Manual code review in either Java, C# or Python. \r\n2. Properties of TLS. What it supports. (Basically everything about it except for explaining the TLS handshake. Which was strange that the interviewer did not want that explaination)\r\n3. Manual threat model.\r\n4. API implementation and design.\r\n5. Authentication for APIs\r\n6. Implementing TLS\r\n7. Securing a SQL DB\r\n8. CSRF\r\n9. SQL Injection\r\n10. Cipher Suites\r\n11. Hashing vs Encryption", "answer": []}, {"key": 629, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Yahoo", "date": "19 January 2021", "question": "the engineer clearly wanted me to come to some sort of pre-conceived key distribution system that I was supposed to come up with on a white board given extremely vague requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 630, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "19 January 2021", "question": "Questions were based on the profile. Started from basics to advance levels", "answer": []}, {"key": 631, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Walmart", "date": "19 January 2021", "question": "Name one thing you would implement as a security policy... or something like that.", "answer": []}, {"key": 632, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "New Relic", "date": "18 January 2021", "question": "What is a Server Side Request Forgery attack?", "answer": ["A vulnerability in a web server that exists due to a lack of malicious user input detection, sanitation, and validation checks. SSRF vulnerabilities don't validate the user provided URL endpoints before processing/calling the URL endpoints. This allows a bad-actor to make requests to bogon IP addresses (127.0.0.1, 169.254.0.0/16, fe80::1, etc) which often can force the web server to reveal sensitive data and website administration pages that only run on localhost to a bad-actor on the public internet. Less"]}, {"key": 633, "position": "Security Engineer Or Contractor Only", "company": "Kubota Tractor", "date": "18 January 2021", "question": "Industry standard questions that every candidate expect to be asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 634, "position": "Security Engineer Or Contractor Only", "company": "Kubota Tractor", "date": "18 January 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself ?", "answer": ["I told them about my self"]}, {"key": 635, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cofense", "date": "18 January 2021", "question": "What cloud technologies are you familiar with?", "answer": []}, {"key": 636, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Virtual1", "date": "16 January 2021", "question": "They were asking about my Network background (Firewalls mostly) and  about information security standards.", "answer": []}, {"key": 637, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Vistra Energy", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "From a security standpoint, iPhone or Android?", "answer": ["iPhone for security means because they control hardware, and their app store controls software. Less"]}, {"key": 638, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Flipkart", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "Tried to showcase that i dont know things and he knows everything", "answer": ["i tried explaining where he was wrong by logic, he could not give logic to his own question. Less"]}, {"key": 639, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Flipkart", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "Taunted if i have cleared cissp [world renowned certificate] by just reading one book and was easy to clear just by reading.", "answer": ["if it was easy why he didnt clear it himself. None of them was cissp certified"]}, {"key": 640, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Flipkart", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "Concern over 4 job switches in 7 year", "answer": ["again why only employee gets the blame? Arent company also to be blamed. Wont they layoff people? I got it twice so am i to be blamed for their politics? 2009- layoff, corona-layoff, US ban- layoff, no rain -layoff but they wont blame them but us. Ironically Less"]}, {"key": 641, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Flipkart", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "Concern over gaps in education", "answer": ["not all are lucky and born with golden spoon. Gaps depend upon financial, emotional and family conditions. Its called struggle in life. Not sure what is the concern as if i had been doing wrong things that would be caught in BGV before hiring. Less"]}, {"key": 642, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Bright Health", "date": "15 January 2021", "question": "What motivates you to be inspired? (This one says it all, they are looking for the right candidates not just one that fills a roll).", "answer": ["I am inspired by the opportunity to make a difference, I am inspired by needs I can meet and by the challenges that I encounter that help me grow along the way. Less"]}, {"key": 643, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Baidu", "date": "14 January 2021", "question": "Proposing a sorting algorithm and write a simple code.", "answer": ["Bubble sort and quick sort algorithm."]}, {"key": 644, "position": "Security Engineer - Junior -/Data Loss Prevention", "company": "Capgemini Engineering", "date": "13 January 2021", "question": "Qual foi o projecto que mais gostei de fazer e sobre o que?", "answer": []}, {"key": 645, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "What my experience with specific technologies were", "answer": []}, {"key": 646, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Adobe", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "Why Adobe?\r\nBe prepared to answer a variety of security situations.", "answer": []}, {"key": 647, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Adobe", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "Why Adobe?\r\nBe prepared to answer a variety of security situations.", "answer": []}, {"key": 648, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Honey", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "Run of the mill security questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 649, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Honey", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "Run of the mill security questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 650, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Capgemini", "date": "12 January 2021", "question": "STP, VPN,  BGP, OSPF", "answer": []}, {"key": 651, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "L\u00ednea Directa", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "Has trabajado con ... ? (F5, Palo A, Cisco...)", "answer": []}, {"key": 652, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Spotify", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "What are your biggest strengths?\n\nWhat was your biggest failure?", "answer": []}, {"key": 653, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Trustwave", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "Describe what are egghunters and their use in exploit development.\r\nCan you describe the different segments on a debugger?\r\nHow's your proficiency on IDA? Can you describe how you would find bugs on an x86 binary?", "answer": []}, {"key": 654, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flatiron Health", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "Give me an example of a CTF challenge that you worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 655, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ground Control", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "Have you use ISO27001 before and describe it", "answer": []}, {"key": 656, "position": "Embedded Security Engineer", "company": "ALTEN", "date": "11 January 2021", "question": "It mainly involved discussing my interests, past experiences with embedded systems. Also as the role is of a consultant, was asked about previous experiences with clients.", "answer": []}, {"key": 657, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "10 January 2021", "question": "Tell me what was the most recent code you wrote?", "answer": []}, {"key": 658, "position": "Sr. Network Security Engineer", "company": "Jane Street", "date": "9 January 2021", "question": "What is ECN bit used for?", "answer": []}, {"key": 659, "position": "Network and Security Engineer", "company": "Landa Labs", "date": "9 January 2021", "question": "Describe a project you managed end-to-end.", "answer": []}, {"key": 660, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Indeed", "date": "9 January 2021", "question": "Describe the difference between tcp and udp.", "answer": []}, {"key": 661, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Viasat", "date": "8 January 2021", "question": "Some questions regarding my past projects, then some language specific questions, and finally some questions relating to cybersecurity.", "answer": []}, {"key": 662, "position": "Security Test Engineer", "company": "SAP", "date": "7 January 2021", "question": "Na", "answer": []}, {"key": 663, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Macquarie Group", "date": "6 January 2021", "question": "Basic question from network security", "answer": ["All practical questions"]}, {"key": 664, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "5 January 2021", "question": "What is traceroute? Explain it in details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 665, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "4 January 2021", "question": "Are  you comfortable in rotational shifts", "answer": []}, {"key": 666, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "4 January 2021", "question": "So tell me about yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 667, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "4 January 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself working in the near future(Something like that)", "answer": []}, {"key": 668, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "4 January 2021", "question": "Are comfortable  with a 2.5-year bond", "answer": []}, {"key": 669, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "4 January 2021", "question": "Simple Straight forward question regarding TPRM", "answer": []}, {"key": 670, "position": "Software Engineer - Security Response", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "3 January 2021", "question": "I was asked about various web application vulnerabilities and how to mitigate them. The questions were asked form the CWE Top 25 and OWASP Top 10.", "answer": []}, {"key": 671, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cerner", "date": "2 January 2021", "question": "No Interview question because I never reached through that process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 672, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "2 January 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself, Why do you want to work here? Walk me through your resume, Difference between data at rest and data in transit, Difference between SOC Type 1 and Type 2, Your experience with Programming, Cloud related questions,", "answer": []}, {"key": 673, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "30 December 2020", "question": "First interview: explain recursion to a child.\nwhy microsoft? what news did you hear about us?\nwhat makes code great?\n\nsecond interview:\nfriendly introduction,  books you read about software engineering.\nquestion - given an array of 0 1 and '?' print all combinations where '?' is 0 or 1.\n\nsecond technical interview:\nHow does ActionListener work in GUI?\nHow does multithreading work? how to synchronize threads?\nHow does communication between two computers over a network work?\nHow does serialization work?\nThere were a lot of weird theoretical esoteric questions like this and the interviewer gave me only 5 minutes to complete a coding question: given a binary tree - scan and save it to a file so that you could restore it.", "answer": ["Recursion to a child - two mirrors, matryoshka dolls.\nArray with '0' '1' and '?' - Backtracking.\nBooks I read - GOF design patterns. Less"]}, {"key": 674, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "Tell me about your personal portfolio website. what stack did you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 675, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "Can you tell me what is your responsibilities on your internship?", "answer": []}, {"key": 676, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "How to secure the database, even if the credential is leaked?", "answer": []}, {"key": 677, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "Can you draw a cloud environment and how to secure it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 678, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "Can you tell me your Thesis?", "answer": ["My thesis was about crypto system and cloud storage, then I explained it"]}, {"key": 679, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Tokopedia", "date": "29 December 2020", "question": "How to secure the inbound connection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 680, "position": "Co-Op Security Engineer", "company": "Canadian Natural", "date": "28 December 2020", "question": "Name a time you made a mistake and how did you overcome it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 681, "position": "Hardware Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "23 December 2020", "question": "give u a case and ask you find security flaw", "answer": []}, {"key": 682, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 December 2020", "question": "How to change the static IP on a PC?", "answer": []}, {"key": 683, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Yelp", "date": "21 December 2020", "question": "Hackerrank challenge of 1st phase - similar to the training challenge you are given. Computation of the \"Jaccard index\" based on data which are in JSON format.", "answer": []}, {"key": 684, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Yelp", "date": "21 December 2020", "question": "Hackerrank challenge of 2nd phase - Live Coding. Given a JSON set in the form of: '{\"receiver\": \"a@b.com\", \"messsage\": \"[reducted],\" \"sender\": \"c@b.com\"}', compute the email address/-es with the most unique senders and/or receivers. Use `assert` to validate your answers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 685, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "PORR", "date": "21 December 2020", "question": "They didn't ask questions, it was just in general talking from the hiring manager.", "answer": []}, {"key": 686, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Meta", "date": "21 December 2020", "question": "What are the types of XSS attacks, what are the differences.", "answer": []}, {"key": 687, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "17 December 2020", "question": "Why are you looking to leave your current role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 688, "position": "Security Systems Engineer", "company": "University of Redlands", "date": "17 December 2020", "question": "what protocol does DNS use", "answer": ["It use UDP protocol and port 53"]}, {"key": 689, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AppFolio", "date": "16 December 2020", "question": "IDS/IPS\r\nSQL injection, Queries, and payloads\r\nXSS, Queries, and payloads\r\nUse case and how to implement Reflected XSS\r\nMetasploit and its commands\r\nHow to add a target and how to use Nmap in Metasploit\r\nWhat is Reverse shell\r\nAWS and services\r\nHow to deploy a web application in the cloud\r\nDocker, Container, Kubernetes\r\nHow do you rate yourself for programming languages like python, C, C++.", "answer": []}, {"key": 690, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Tide", "date": "16 December 2020", "question": "- What are the tasks of a pentester?\n- CSRF on S3?\n- Cloud Security: Shared trust model?", "answer": []}, {"key": 691, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MTSI", "date": "15 December 2020", "question": "The main question was in regard to the company values", "answer": ["I reviewed the website prior to the interview and remembered the values."]}, {"key": 692, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "15 December 2020", "question": "What would you use to order a log of traffic by date?", "answer": []}, {"key": 693, "position": "Principal Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Questrade", "date": "13 December 2020", "question": "What else is there in a PodSecurityPolicy?", "answer": ["readOnly, etc.... I think he had just switched to the kubernetes documentation on PodSecurityPolicy by now.. Less"]}, {"key": 694, "position": "Principal Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Questrade", "date": "13 December 2020", "question": "How else do you secure your kubernetes clusters?", "answer": ["I asked him if he had something specific in mind, or he's just looking for answers such ad: identity and access management, networkpolicy, hardening, etc... Less"]}, {"key": 695, "position": "Principal Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Questrade", "date": "13 December 2020", "question": "What do you use a PodSecurityPolicy for?", "answer": ["To set security policies for a Pod, such as whether a pod should run as a root or not. Less"]}, {"key": 696, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cvent", "date": "13 December 2020", "question": "Encryption vs hashing. API integrals, simple programming question", "answer": []}, {"key": 697, "position": "Security Engineer - User Fraud", "company": "Spotify", "date": "11 December 2020", "question": "Symmetric/asymmetric cryptography, CSRF, Code review of an authentication function.", "answer": []}, {"key": 698, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AppFolio", "date": "10 December 2020", "question": "DevSecOps familiarity setting up application security tools with the current SDLC", "answer": []}, {"key": 699, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Zapier", "date": "10 December 2020", "question": "The one I liked most: for users, I suggested a complex and long (20+ characters) password and no expiration. For API keys I suggested short-lived keys with frequent rotation. Why do I have a difference in the suggestion for passwords and api keys?", "answer": []}, {"key": 700, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ANZ Bank", "date": "9 December 2020", "question": "First question was why I want to work for them. Second they asked me if I know about AGILE work culture. Third question was some question regarding team play.", "answer": ["ANZ is the largest bank in south pacific. I didn't knew about AGILE. I threw in some intern experience in which I displayed team play. Less"]}, {"key": 701, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "8 December 2020", "question": "Networking questions in depth? and network security firewall, stp, utp and more", "answer": []}, {"key": 702, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Jio", "date": "8 December 2020", "question": "Encryption techniques, Opps, DB questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 703, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Splunk", "date": "8 December 2020", "question": "Questions were related to my background and seemed to be more about getting to know me as a person.", "answer": ["Honestly", "Any specifics?"]}, {"key": 704, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Davidson Consulting", "date": "8 December 2020", "question": "Quel est votre qualit\u00e9 la plus importante?", "answer": ["L'adaptation", "Adaptation rapide"]}, {"key": 705, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Davidson Consulting", "date": "8 December 2020", "question": "Quelle est la qualit\u00e9 la plus importante que vous voulez trouver dans un collaborateur?", "answer": ["La rigueur"]}, {"key": 706, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "7 December 2020", "question": "Tell me about yourself/ previous exp.", "answer": ["linkedin", "In these sorts of interviews you really need to drill down and understand what the interviewer is looking for.\r\n\r\n\r\nA good way to simulate a real interview experience is to do a mock with one of the Affirm  Security Engineer experts on Prepfully, rated super strongly on TrustPilot...\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 707, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "7 December 2020", "question": "Q: What would you do to harden a given environment?\nQ: Tell us about your security experience?\nQ: Analyze this code snippet and tell me what's suspicious here?", "answer": []}, {"key": 708, "position": "Security Systems Engineer", "company": "SECOM", "date": "5 December 2020", "question": "Can work overtime, Saturday work OT", "answer": []}, {"key": 709, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Klarna", "date": "5 December 2020", "question": "You will get URL and have to find several vulnerabilities and prepare a report.", "answer": []}, {"key": 710, "position": "Graduate - Software, Platform Or Security Engineer", "company": "BP", "date": "4 December 2020", "question": "None of the questions available.", "answer": []}, {"key": 711, "position": "Senior Security Developer", "company": "SAP", "date": "4 December 2020", "question": "What is your Motivation for joining SAP", "answer": []}, {"key": 712, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "3 December 2020", "question": "Nothing was asked as the interviewer was a no-show", "answer": []}, {"key": 713, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Maybank", "date": "1 December 2020", "question": "Linux command, network troubleshooting steps", "answer": []}, {"key": 714, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hopin", "date": "1 December 2020", "question": "General security questions about OWASP, security automation, pentesting.", "answer": []}, {"key": 715, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "30 November 2020", "question": "Networking and security questions\r\nCoding algorithm question", "answer": []}, {"key": 716, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "29 November 2020", "question": "What do you do, the incident reported firefox version was infected by malware.", "answer": []}, {"key": 717, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Asiacell", "date": "26 November 2020", "question": "What is HTTP request smuggling", "answer": []}, {"key": 718, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DXC Technology", "date": "25 November 2020", "question": "Product specific questions, mostly.", "answer": []}, {"key": 719, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "23 November 2020", "question": "Tell about two repetitive task that you have at your work?\nwhat is week cipher? Tell about the security mechanism that you have used for webservice and API  ? I have application that is running on the server, and you see some attack in you application from specific system you need configure security  without disturb this server, how did you do that?", "answer": []}, {"key": 720, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Acronis", "date": "23 November 2020", "question": "Describe the network flow of a packet.", "answer": []}, {"key": 721, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Amaris.Ai", "date": "20 November 2020", "question": "Open-ended question: how would you do (something technical) differently?", "answer": []}, {"key": 722, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Amaris.Ai", "date": "20 November 2020", "question": "Debugging question: given a stack trace, can you find out what is wrong?", "answer": []}, {"key": 723, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Amaris.Ai", "date": "20 November 2020", "question": "Coding question which you can answer in pseudo code to test your logic.", "answer": []}, {"key": 724, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "3M", "date": "18 November 2020", "question": "My accomplishments from my previous positions and  how I handled difficult managers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 725, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citrix", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "CSRF attack and defense, Cloud security, Mobile Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 726, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iCIMS", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "Tell me about a time or experience you had with X product and what you used to solve a problem with the solution?", "answer": []}, {"key": 727, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iCIMS", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "How do you stay up to date with the latest in Security Trends?", "answer": []}, {"key": 728, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Updox", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "What do you do if your upper management doesn't support security objectives?", "answer": ["I answered that you present the risks by outlining security incident likelihoods and impacts.  If qualitative analysis does not sway upper management, quantitative methods can be used to better illustrate the potential for negative financial impact to the business.   I also added that in the end, it is upper managements role (CISO, et al) to accept security risk...which they seemed to disagree with. Less"]}, {"key": 729, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Updox", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "What is your preferred data classification framework?", "answer": ["Gave a non-committal answer explaining that is very organization specific.   Told them that I believe data classification should not be overly complicated if they want buy-in from all parts of the business - especially for SMBs that are growing. Less"]}, {"key": 730, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Optum", "date": "16 November 2020", "question": "Questions from cybersecurity, networking, Data structure  .", "answer": []}, {"key": 731, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "SpaceX", "date": "13 November 2020", "question": "Create a technical presentation on a project you've done", "answer": []}, {"key": 732, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Pampered Chef", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Basic HR questions for initial phone screen.", "answer": []}, {"key": 733, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Pampered Chef", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Basic HR questions for initial phone screen.", "answer": []}, {"key": 734, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Explain the different types of firewalls", "answer": []}, {"key": 735, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Difference between unit and integration tests, and when would you use each?", "answer": []}, {"key": 736, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "General questions around docker security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 737, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Examples from top 10 OWASP", "answer": []}, {"key": 738, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Do you know the OSI model and it's various layers?", "answer": []}, {"key": 739, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "What is TLS? Does it use public key or symmetric key cryptography?", "answer": []}, {"key": 740, "position": "Security Network Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "Just a general first HR appointment, talk about you and your experience, salary scheme, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 741, "position": "Adv Cyber Security Engineer/Arch", "company": "Honeywell", "date": "12 November 2020", "question": "What did I do on my last (current in that moment) job?", "answer": ["I usually starde my day doing this and that..."]}, {"key": 742, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "9 November 2020", "question": "What is stack overflow attack?\nCan we perform that attack on JAVA programs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 743, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "9 November 2020", "question": "NDA, Can't share the interview question", "answer": []}, {"key": 744, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Couchbase", "date": "8 November 2020", "question": "Behavioral and Code reviews are the main questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 745, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Moffitt Cancer Center", "date": "6 November 2020", "question": "They will mention things on your resume to make sure you know what you're talking about.", "answer": ["I had a couple things on there that I was in the process of learning, so I had them on my resume (when I really shouldn't have).\r\nMy answer wasn't nearly as solid as I would have liked.\r\nmake sure you can back up every skill on your resume well. Less"]}, {"key": 746, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Moffitt Cancer Center", "date": "6 November 2020", "question": "They will mention things on your resume to make sure you know what you're talking about.", "answer": ["I had a couple things on there that I was in the process of learning, so I had them on my resume (when I really shouldn't have).\r\nMy answer wasn't nearly as solid as I would have liked.\r\nmake sure you can back up every skill on your resume well. Less"]}, {"key": 747, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "5 November 2020", "question": "Technical background and experience on SIEM integration. They are looking for developers with security knowledge not the other way around.", "answer": ["Through questions like this, interviewers are mostly trying to test your skillset (and its relevance to the role) as robustly as possible, so be prepared for multiple offshoots and followups.\r\n\r\n\r\nIt could be a useful exercise to do mocks with friends or colleagues in Affirm to get a real sense of what the interview is actually like. Alternatively Prepfully has a ton of Affirm  Security Engineer experts who provide mock interviews for a pretty reasonable amount.\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 748, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Brex", "date": "4 November 2020", "question": "LC Easy, Valid Parentheses problem", "answer": []}, {"key": 749, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "4 November 2020", "question": "The difference between XSS types (phone interview)", "answer": []}, {"key": 750, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "3 November 2020", "question": "what makes you interested in this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 751, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "2 November 2020", "question": "What classes did you take?\r\nWhats a ideal role for you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 752, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "2 November 2020", "question": "What are some port numbers and their functions", "answer": []}, {"key": 753, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ST Engineering", "date": "31 October 2020", "question": "What is your skillset and what are you good at?", "answer": []}, {"key": 754, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Jio", "date": "30 October 2020", "question": "What is OWASP?\r\nHow does WPF work?", "answer": []}, {"key": 755, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Niantic", "date": "29 October 2020", "question": "Various questions focused on cloud security and client security.", "answer": ["Through questions like this, interviewers are mostly trying to test your skillset (and its relevance to the role) as robustly as possible, so be prepared for multiple offshoots and followups.\r\n\r\n\r\nIt could be a useful exercise to do mocks with friends or colleagues in Niantic to get a real sense of what the interview is actually like. Alternatively Prepfully has a ton of Niantic  Security Engineer experts who provide mock interviews for a pretty reasonable amount.\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 756, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "SoFi", "date": "28 October 2020", "question": "How do you plan on setting up the security program?", "answer": []}, {"key": 757, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "28 October 2020", "question": "Linux heavy on the technical interview, foundational knowledge really. Trying to gauge experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 758, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Fivetran", "date": "27 October 2020", "question": "How would you secure a containerized environment?", "answer": []}, {"key": 759, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Code42", "date": "27 October 2020", "question": "Knowledge of insider threat, DLP, and End Point", "answer": []}, {"key": 760, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Sourcegraph", "date": "27 October 2020", "question": "Write a vulnerability impact assessment on an old, well known, vulnerability.", "answer": []}, {"key": 761, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "26 October 2020", "question": "Do you have experience with SIEM implementations?", "answer": []}, {"key": 762, "position": "App Security Engineer", "company": "Viagogo", "date": "26 October 2020", "question": "Bugbounty, Vulnerabilities found, public, vulnerabilities found.", "answer": ["Basic Sec Knowledge"]}, {"key": 763, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Yelp", "date": "26 October 2020", "question": "How would you design x, how would you exploit y, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 764, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Procore Technologies", "date": "25 October 2020", "question": "General talk about experience and interest in switching. Nothing outstanding and some focus on my current company focus", "answer": []}, {"key": 765, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Innovaccer", "date": "24 October 2020", "question": "Situation based questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 766, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Innovaccer", "date": "24 October 2020", "question": "Incident Responder Questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 767, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Innovaccer", "date": "24 October 2020", "question": "Different types of threats and cyber attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 768, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Innovaccer", "date": "24 October 2020", "question": "Basic cybersecurity questions for eg. Ports, OSI Tcp/ip model. Cyber kill chain etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 769, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Innovaccer", "date": "24 October 2020", "question": "SIEM basics, architecture, working. Etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 770, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dream11", "date": "23 October 2020", "question": "Q. Doing a vulnerability assessment of their internal website and submitting a detailed report.", "answer": []}, {"key": 771, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "CSS Corporation", "date": "23 October 2020", "question": "Same as process", "answer": []}, {"key": 772, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "JASINT Consulting and Technologies", "date": "22 October 2020", "question": "What strengths do you have that would benefit some of our current contracts?", "answer": []}, {"key": 773, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 October 2020", "question": "About network and security and your Previous career", "answer": []}, {"key": 774, "position": "Security Consulting Engineer ()", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "20 October 2020", "question": "What are the layers of the OSI model and what do they do?", "answer": ["I named the layers in order and mentioned how they interact with each other, what they use (e.x. MAC addresses vs. IP addresses), and example use cases. Less"]}, {"key": 775, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "monday.com", "date": "20 October 2020", "question": "Technical questions about OWASP top 10 and cryptography.", "answer": []}, {"key": 776, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "18 October 2020", "question": "Questions about Docker security", "answer": []}, {"key": 777, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Form3 Financial Cloud", "date": "18 October 2020", "question": "Describe TLS handshake", "answer": []}, {"key": 778, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Loadsmart", "date": "18 October 2020", "question": "General questions:\r\n\r\n* \"Talk about yourself.\"\r\n* Main good and bad qualities.\r\n* What you like to do in your free time.\r\n* How your current/last team sees you.\r\n* What you want for the future.\r\n\r\nTechnical questions:\r\n\r\n* Difference between stateful/ stateless firewalls.\r\n* Difference between TCP/UDP.\r\n* Some questions about ACL and routers on AWS.\r\n* What is XSS? And how to mitigate and avoid them.\r\n* What is SQL injection and how to avoid them.\r\n* Questions about email phishing.\r\n* Questions about DDoS.\r\n* Things to consider to develop secure applications.", "answer": []}, {"key": 779, "position": "Security Assurance Engineer", "company": "FactSet", "date": "14 October 2020", "question": "There was a whiteboard question asking me to implement a block cipher at a high level.", "answer": []}, {"key": 780, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "13 October 2020", "question": "No questions asked for this round.", "answer": []}, {"key": 781, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Zipwhip", "date": "12 October 2020", "question": "How to secure multiple AWS accounts", "answer": []}, {"key": 782, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Zipwhip", "date": "12 October 2020", "question": "Conducting Threat Modeling on a given scenario", "answer": []}, {"key": 783, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "12 October 2020", "question": "how would describe recursion to a seven year old kid?\r\ntalk about a project you worked on.", "answer": []}, {"key": 784, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "9 October 2020", "question": "1 interview w/recruiter, 1 technical interview w/engineer, 1 technical interview w/would-be manager.", "answer": []}, {"key": 785, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "7 October 2020", "question": "They did not ask anything.", "answer": []}, {"key": 786, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BairesDev", "date": "7 October 2020", "question": "You have to do several exams that are not even related to the technologies and fields you are applying to. \r\n\r\nIt seems that HR doesn't know about the computer engineering world.", "answer": []}, {"key": 787, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "7 October 2020", "question": "Take an integer array of unknown size and return true if any 3 numbers add up to 0", "answer": ["Didn't really answer it. Kind of lost the desire to move forward after the opening question. Less"]}, {"key": 788, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 October 2020", "question": "Find security bugs in given code", "answer": []}, {"key": 789, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 October 2020", "question": "With a given number, find the least number of operations needed to make the number. Only 3 types of operation are allowed: +1, -1, *2. Try to optimize your code", "answer": []}, {"key": 790, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 October 2020", "question": "Technical whiteboard discussion on topics found during reviewing the resume", "answer": []}, {"key": 791, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 October 2020", "question": "Question related queue using array in C", "answer": []}, {"key": 792, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flatiron Health", "date": "4 October 2020", "question": "Describe what happens when you visit a website", "answer": []}, {"key": 793, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "3 October 2020", "question": "How to create a botnet", "answer": ["I didn\u2019t know"]}, {"key": 794, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Indeed", "date": "2 October 2020", "question": "How would you communicate and collaborate with other individuals?", "answer": []}, {"key": 795, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Indeed", "date": "2 October 2020", "question": "Examine this data flow diagram and these API structures and describe the security controls and questions you would ask someone", "answer": []}, {"key": 796, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "2 October 2020", "question": "Description of the traceroute command to the level of protocol and its differences with Windows' tracert.", "answer": []}, {"key": 797, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Open Systems", "date": "28 September 2020", "question": "Auf was sind sie am meisten stolz?", "answer": []}, {"key": 798, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Electricity Supply Board (ESB)", "date": "26 September 2020", "question": "Scenario based questions", "answer": ["As per my previous experience"]}, {"key": 799, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Endurance International Group", "date": "26 September 2020", "question": "Cryptography, Symmetric key and asymmetric key , concepts of Networking -OSI layers ,etc..", "answer": []}, {"key": 800, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "22 September 2020", "question": "Experience with RMF or Nist 800-53", "answer": []}, {"key": 801, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Endurance International Group", "date": "22 September 2020", "question": "PII full form?(example1) \r\nPOP3 port number?(example2)", "answer": []}, {"key": 802, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BairesDev", "date": "19 September 2020", "question": "First of all, before any interview they require you to complete some online tests.", "answer": []}, {"key": 803, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Expedia Group", "date": "19 September 2020", "question": "Describe a time facing difficulties , If ressources was available what project do you want ro build, What can prevent a web app to be available if the server is running perfectly \r\n\r\nWell known protocol", "answer": []}, {"key": 804, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cognizant Technology Solutions", "date": "17 September 2020", "question": "about cyber security and information secuirty", "answer": []}, {"key": 805, "position": "Principal Information Security Engineer", "company": "Delivery Hero", "date": "16 September 2020", "question": "Explain XSS", "answer": []}, {"key": 806, "position": "Game Security Engineer", "company": "Rockstar Games", "date": "14 September 2020", "question": "None, never heard back from recruiter to schedule the interview.", "answer": []}, {"key": 807, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "11 September 2020", "question": "The phone call interview was just basic questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 808, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "10 September 2020", "question": "Why IBM? what can you bring to us company?", "answer": []}, {"key": 809, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Cobb EMC", "date": "10 September 2020", "question": "1st- Recruiter call discuss pay and asked basic network security questions. Use job requirements via job posting.\n\n2nd- Teams video call with the (3) hiring team.  Asked the following:\n\nNetwork Security Interview Questions\nFor Candidate\nNetwork Security Interview Questions\n1)What is Ransomware?\n2) How does ransomware work?\n3) Can you give me some Ransomware variants?\nPhishing Network Security Interview Questions\n4) What is Phishing?\n5) How does phishing work?\nFirewall Network Security Interview Questions\n6) What are the benefits of the firewall?\n7) What is UTM firewall?\n8) What is Next-generation firewall (NGFW)?\n9) What is Threat-focused NGFW?\nMalware Network Security Interview Questions\n10) What is Malware?\n11) What is the difference between a virus and malware? \n12) What are Worms?\n13) What is Trojan Virus?\n14) What is Spyware?\n15) What is Adware?\nVPN Network Security Interview Questions\n16) Why do we use Virtual Private Network?\n17) How does a virtual private network (VPN) work?\n18) What is secure remote access?\n19) What are the different types of VPNs?\n20) What is Site-to-site VPN?\n21) What is Spam?\nDDoS Attack Network Security Interview Questions\n22) What Is a DDoS Attack?\n23) What are the types of DDoS Attacks?\n24) What is UDP flood?\n25) What is SYN flood?\n26) What is Ping of Death? \nNAC IT Network Security Interview Questions\n27) What Is Shadow IT?\n28) What Is Network Access Control?\n29) Why is it important to have a NAC solution?\n30) What Is Data Loss Prevention (DLP)?\n31) How does DLP work?\n32) What is Cloud Security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 810, "position": "Security Systems Engineer", "company": "", "date": "8 September 2020", "question": "How do you handle troubleshooting devices without any superior around you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 811, "position": "Security Systems Engineer", "company": "", "date": "8 September 2020", "question": "How do you handle stress?", "answer": []}, {"key": 812, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Citrix", "date": "8 September 2020", "question": "Round 1 \u2013 1hr:\n\nNetwork Pentest:\nSSH Brute force\nSensitive Ports\nScanning\nSSL/TLS (Explanation, Implementation, Attacks)\nDNS (Attacks and mitigation) (Levels of attacks)\nDHCP (Attack and mitigation)\nDMZ\nCrypto modes\nSymmetric & Asymmetric (In-depth) \n\nBinary Exploitation:\nIDA, GDB\nBuffer Overflow\nFormat string vulnerability (Project, Explanation, Attacks, Flaws, Patching and Attack Submission in PHP) \n\nRound 2 - 1hr\nThe mechanism behind DNS Cache Poisoning\nWhat is SSL/TLS, working, handshake, and stripping attacks.\nCSRF (In-depth)\nXXE (In-depth)\nHTTP header\nhost header\nReferrer header\nCookie header\nAnti-CSRF tokens\nWhy and how you use Anti-CSRF tokens? Can it be placed anywhere in the header or should be under the cookie header?\n\nRound 3 \u2013 1hr:\nCaptcha Bypassing (Explanation, Suggestion and Mitigation Techniques)\nFormat String Vulnerability (Real-time attacks)\nSSRF (In-depth) (Explanation, Suggestion, and Mitigation)\nDMZ (Where to place it and how to configure)\nDNS (Link between SSRF and DNS)", "answer": []}, {"key": 813, "position": "Platform Security Engineer", "company": "Gear4music", "date": "8 September 2020", "question": "Go through how my experience relates to the role", "answer": []}, {"key": 814, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Cobb EMC", "date": "8 September 2020", "question": "Network Security Interview Questions\nFor Candidate\nNetwork Security Interview Questions\n1)What is Ransomware?\n2) How does ransomware work?\n3) Can you give me some Ransomware variants?\nPhishing Network Security Interview Questions\n4) What is Phishing?\n5) How does phishing work?\nFirewall Network Security Interview Questions\n6) What are the benefits of the firewall?\n7) What is UTM firewall?\n8) What is Next-generation firewall (NGFW)?\n9) What is Threat-focused NGFW?\nMalware Network Security Interview Questions\n10) What is Malware?\n11) What is the difference between a virus and malware? \n12) What are Worms?\n13) What is Trojan Virus?\n14) What is Spyware?\n15) What is Adware?\nVPN Network Security Interview Questions\n16) Why do we use Virtual Private Network?\n17) How does a virtual private network (VPN) work?\n18) What is secure remote access?\n19) What are the different types of VPNs?\n20) What is Site-to-site VPN?\n21) What is Spam?\nDDoS Attack Network Security Interview Questions\n22) What Is a DDoS Attack?\n23) What are the types of DDoS Attacks?\n24) What is UDP flood?\n25) What is SYN flood?\n26) What is Ping of Death? \nNAC IT Network Security Interview Questions\n27) What Is Shadow IT?\n28) What Is Network Access Control?\n29) Why is it important to have a NAC solution?\n30) What Is Data Loss Prevention (DLP)?\n31) How does DLP work?\n32) What is Cloud Security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 815, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "7 September 2020", "question": "Mainly focused on what you have done so far and whatever you wrote in your resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 816, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adjust", "date": "7 September 2020", "question": "General questions to test your experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 817, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adjust", "date": "6 September 2020", "question": "The interview consisted of general questions which test your development experience and security related knowledge in order to assess your suitability for the role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 818, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Blackbaud", "date": "4 September 2020", "question": "Salary expectations, start date, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 819, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Clarity Innovations (MD)", "date": "3 September 2020", "question": "Questions about my history and experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 820, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "3 September 2020", "question": "Explain ssl or ssh and break it down in as much detail as you can.", "answer": ["In these sorts of interviews you really need to drill down and understand what the interviewer is looking for.\r\n\r\n\r\nA good way to simulate a real interview experience is to do a mock with one of the Snap  Information Security Engineer experts on Prepfully, rated super strongly on TrustPilot...\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 821, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "3 September 2020", "question": "Do you have any questions for me - Right off the cuff", "answer": ["It's essential to demonstrate that you can really go deep... there are plenty of followup questions and (sometimes tangential) angles to explore.\r\n\r\n\r\nThere's a lot of  Information Security Engineer experts who've worked at Snap, who provide this sort of practice through mock interviews. There's a whole list of them curated on Prepfully.\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 822, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "CrowdStrike", "date": "2 September 2020", "question": "What is your expected total compensation?", "answer": []}, {"key": 823, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "31 August 2020", "question": "How would you design an audit logger?", "answer": ["This is a systems design interview question, so if you know about micro-service architecture, databases, scaling, and caching, that would be relatively enough to answer it. Less", "There's a lot of elements to typically cover in these questions, clarifications, scoping, making sure you're answering the actual question the interviewer is looking for you to answer, etc.\r\n\r\n\r\nCould be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Prepfully DigitalOcean  Security Engineer experts... they've worked in the role so they clearly know how to get through the interview.\r\n\r\n\r\nprepfully.com/practice-interviews Less"]}, {"key": 824, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro", "date": "31 August 2020", "question": "Questions are anything about the position your applying to and also about your skills.", "answer": []}, {"key": 825, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intermedia", "date": "31 August 2020", "question": "What is port for RDP?", "answer": ["3389"]}, {"key": 826, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intermedia", "date": "31 August 2020", "question": "Difference between TCP and UDP?", "answer": ["TCP is a connection-oriented protocol, whereas UDP is a connectionless protocol"]}, {"key": 827, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "29 August 2020", "question": "They covered the basics and then had follow up questions to make sure you understood the fundamentals on a deep level.", "answer": ["What type of questions came in for the virtual interview? Any scripting/Coding?"]}, {"key": 828, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "28 August 2020", "question": "Why you want to join an IT company from mechanical field.", "answer": ["coz i am interested in the field"]}, {"key": 829, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Google", "date": "28 August 2020", "question": "General coding questions and my past experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 830, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intermedia", "date": "28 August 2020", "question": "Ipv4 Local Host\r\nPorts SMTP, RDP, LDAP, HTTPS, IMAP, SSH\r\nQ. Few Linux commands like searching a file etc.\r\nQ. Linux command for disk space or list of files\r\nQ. Successful User Account Login event id\r\nQ. DNS record type for Mail Exchange \r\nQ. Ipv4 Local Host\r\nQ. Ports SMTP, RDP, LDAP, HTTPS, IMAP, SSH", "answer": []}, {"key": 831, "position": "Applications Security Senior Developer", "company": "PokerStars", "date": "26 August 2020", "question": "questions which were not even important enough in a security interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 832, "position": "Applications Security Senior Developer", "company": "PokerStars", "date": "26 August 2020", "question": "css and html version", "answer": []}, {"key": 833, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "LogDNA", "date": "26 August 2020", "question": "various encryption, pipeline management, securing code types of questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 834, "position": "Web Security Engineer", "company": "ByteDance", "date": "24 August 2020", "question": "How many types of XSS do you know.", "answer": []}, {"key": 835, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "CSS Corporation", "date": "22 August 2020", "question": "Tell me about yourself.\r\nTell me about your hobbies.", "answer": []}, {"key": 836, "position": "Senior Principal Security Engineer", "company": "iTCO Solutions", "date": "21 August 2020", "question": "Can you talk on the phone?", "answer": []}, {"key": 837, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "PTC", "date": "18 August 2020", "question": "Networking and python basics and project", "answer": []}, {"key": 838, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Akamai", "date": "18 August 2020", "question": "networking questions mainly about security and ddos attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 839, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "What is your weakness and give an example?", "answer": []}, {"key": 840, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "What does integrity mean to you and give an example of how you applied it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 841, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "What challenges did you overcome?", "answer": []}, {"key": 842, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "What can you bring to this job that you have experience in?", "answer": []}, {"key": 843, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "Tell me about yourself (education/interest in cyber security)", "answer": []}, {"key": 844, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Veeco Instruments", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "Why did you apply to this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 845, "position": "Applications Security Developer/Consultant", "company": "", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "We talked over past projects and they probed to find the technical reasoning behind decisions that were made.", "answer": []}, {"key": 846, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "Walk me through RSA encryption.", "answer": []}, {"key": 847, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MacAndrews & Forbes", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "what are 3 things you implement as soon as you are hired?", "answer": []}, {"key": 848, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "13 August 2020", "question": "What is a NAT? \r\nWhat is a Virtual Private Tunnel? \r\nTell me something about Fortinet Devices.", "answer": []}, {"key": 849, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "12 August 2020", "question": "Explain what Address Resolution Protocol is.", "answer": []}, {"key": 850, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Paytm Labs", "date": "11 August 2020", "question": "What is the difference between encoding, encryption and hashing.", "answer": ["encoding is transforming a string to something more suitable for transfer and is not really meant to hide anything.\r\nEncryption is done to hide things with the purpose or reverting it eventually, like to transfer data or even for identification.\r\nHashing is not meant to be reversable and is used to validate things, like file integrity or passwords. Less"]}, {"key": 851, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "Mambu", "date": "10 August 2020", "question": "The fundamental principles of Information Security, AWS Security, Kubernetes, a couple of AWS system design and scenario-based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 852, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Funding Circle", "date": "8 August 2020", "question": "How would you secure specific technologies, secure design questions, scenario-based discussions mostly around collaborating with engineering teams.", "answer": []}, {"key": 853, "position": "Security Engineer Position", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "7 August 2020", "question": "What port does ping use", "answer": ["None"]}, {"key": 854, "position": "Security Engineer Position", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "7 August 2020", "question": "Describe your perfect job and what is a good fit?", "answer": ["Done"]}, {"key": 855, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intermedia", "date": "7 August 2020", "question": "Google -> Networking Protocols and memorize them all", "answer": []}, {"key": 856, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Creditas", "date": "7 August 2020", "question": "As principais foram:\r\n- Se haveria problemas em trabalhar remoto, 100% em home office.\r\n- E tamb\u00e9m se eu conhecia, ou fui indicado por algum tripulante.", "answer": []}, {"key": 857, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ivalua", "date": "6 August 2020", "question": "Multiple classic security-related questions / problems.", "answer": []}, {"key": 858, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "2 August 2020", "question": "what is role based access control?", "answer": []}, {"key": 859, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Citrix", "date": "28 July 2020", "question": "Web apps, Network, CTF, EDR bypass, Exploitation", "answer": []}, {"key": 860, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sysmex America", "date": "24 July 2020", "question": "Questions about work history.\r\nDescription of job/role.\r\nQuestions about personality and value you can bring.", "answer": []}, {"key": 861, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MedImpact", "date": "22 July 2020", "question": "Q: How would you secure XYZ system", "answer": []}, {"key": 862, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "SecPod Technologies", "date": "20 July 2020", "question": "All about Networking | OS | Algorithms and basics you learnt in your college life.", "answer": ["I was not so good in networking. So, I already said them I'll be more interested if they give the chance for my desired field, and they said they'll get in touch if there is ay opening. Less"]}, {"key": 863, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Poshmark", "date": "19 July 2020", "question": "Writing  two Programs with any language", "answer": ["Write a program to find the numbers divisible by 3 and 5 and so on"]}, {"key": 864, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "14 July 2020", "question": "What a was a time when you had to automate something and what was the result?", "answer": []}, {"key": 865, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Dimension Data", "date": "13 July 2020", "question": "How does an SSL VPN work", "answer": []}, {"key": 866, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Capgemini", "date": "13 July 2020", "question": "Stuffs related to palo alto firewall", "answer": ["Explained about packet flow, DNAT, routing"]}, {"key": 867, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Novanta", "date": "11 July 2020", "question": "Why I wanted to take on this job?", "answer": ["Because of their global presence, it give an opportunity to enhance the skill"]}, {"key": 868, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Dotmatics", "date": "8 July 2020", "question": "What are the requirements of ISO 27001?", "answer": []}, {"key": 869, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Dotmatics", "date": "8 July 2020", "question": "How to audit a firewall configuration?", "answer": []}, {"key": 870, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Capgemini", "date": "7 July 2020", "question": "Those who was taken my interview asked me many questions about me and ask about technical questions on networking devices like Routing protocols, Switching Protocols, Firewall, F5 Load Balancer.", "answer": ["I have answered all questions confidently. I had a great experience answering every questions. I also had great experience giving interview. Less"]}]